Ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Hexen is perplexing how they stay alive while staying
Infected, bring energy to the central plane
I'm drugged as cerebral vein because no discomfort ever grows
From rewarding exactly what they've earned
I'm done pretending I'm above it
You speak the...
I don't sip I seal not until every angel finally falls asleep and the demons start whispering and start speaking in caption
This is real life, and you can't sleep walks and feel like it's a personality
What can they do that they haven't done for years
You sell your sins like souvenirs, limited drops on the apology premium tier
Profit from another's tears, Lincoln bio got his good shippiness here
Preach the light then twist the dark, ring like halo, hands full of knives
You built your church from stolen hearts and call to community when the donations arrives
a misconception sure point is it's ain't straight in your direction you think you're safe behind
your life you're grinding your little cleanse your little vibe i see a shadow every time you rise
and it weighs on me like an old acquaintance i'm done floating above it you speak the trigger
angel falls asleep listen demons don't lie they just get promoted this is real
life and your kind's gonna extinct not from death from backbone what can they do
that they haven't for years works in pinning doom yeah mixing weed and how
you want believe you won't need to control back in your hands watch the
curse ignite again a start of something new a hex to you
might be for you.
It's a gift.
That's why we called it the present.
It was a guys man, I have permission to crash out.
Goes already, daddy took the whole crowd.
My God, my voice.
I didn't, I didn't like, I said my Christians like,
they were like, watch the voice.
And I said, oh, because
I was doing this Christine invitation and it takes a lot out of the voice to see a thing that is
I don't know why they're picking on you so bad
You know, I know you're good at handling this up, but I know it gets a little bit much of time, right?
but um
You know that he was going to give you a discount on your best thing $10
I think someone might have paid for it, but make sure you make sure next time you if you go to that channel again, you say
Um, there's a trip and sip on samans channel
Um, I think he said like salmon said oh he's he have a discount ten dollar
I think someone did pay for it and
so make sure
You know you cashed in that uh that best
Just I know I I was on for literally two minutes and like and I said
And then five four three it was like right when I got on
And it's like, okay, so he just made $25 off someone hating me that much to kick me off in like one minute
And like nobody loves me enough to like loves me and I'm not like close me enough
But you know like loves me enough. I know he has he's a yag. He's a totally yag
But you know what at the same time he was playing my clip and everything and there was people in this chat
People in the chat are so rude. There's a lot of people that are just like haters
They're like, oh, this is boring actually is really interesting. What was the video?
They would have shut up for a second not some talking talking over and be to has to say some stupid conscience
I never have I
Don't I don't even know what I have one. Are you going there? Yeah, I
Know he's bought like a bunch of Nike Nike shoes and stuff, but he's just said I don't know
Maybe he's helped him pay his rent. So he doesn't have to be in a park bench or something like that
I don't know all to say. Hey, wherever when everyone wants to send their money go ahead, but
I wish that the hate of me,
I wish that the love of me could, yeah, right,
could be as monetized, I don't know, monetizable,
but it's just like, you know, it seems like it's weird
making people making money off the hate of me so easily.
But whatever, let's move on.
I'm movin' on.
How am I feelin' today?
Feel pretty good.
Pretty good, you know, we watched they were they watched the Alex clip
I mean I had fun at easy's I love easy and you know, double ups is just kind of a dick and stuff
We know that and I think he might have said like oh, he was happy from when I wasn't on the panel and stuff
but I was I
Like I test people sometimes I'm sure I tested you along the way sometimes I said oh, I want to rub your bald head
You're like you probably just gave me a look
Or maybe you laugh or something. I'm not
I want to show the tattoo, but uh, yeah, I wish I was a hate of me. It was as montageable as love or for me
I don't know
That's why I'm like I'm gonna start um selling psyche haters club merchandise and
Then the trolls can wear that and it's like but then it's like, you know
But that's the good thing about sweeping up being around cuz she likes she would like start her own. I know you're not gay
I'm barely gay myself. I'm very barely, but I am
And, you know, not super gay, but, you know, not like,
oh, I'm having, you know, I mean,
I'm having a sex change tomorrow,
but I'm like enough to like, I want to suck some dick.
No, but okay, that was, okay, that went too far
when I said this.
Yeah, they're the ones that freak out, they're so scared.
I know, that's why, and that was a joke,
I'm sorry, I don't know, I don't want to see stupid things.
I'm a little bit, I'm not really even drunk.
I just had a beer, yeah.
And I haven't sucked a dick in over two years.
And so that's probably, it's not by like,
it's kind of, it's by choice, but it's also like,
thank you.
Occasionally it can't be funny, but yeah.
I mean, I'm looking for love in all the wrong places,
looking for love.
Yeah, you know, that kind of country song.
Kind of looking for love in the wrong places sometimes.
And it's like, if I was to date, who I was attracted to,
I would be murdered by the Mexican mafia within a week, I'm pretty sure.
I'm probably tortured and murdered. I mean, I'm going to get down to it.
But I probably would have a smile on my face because I like rough play.
Okay, that was another page. I'm sorry.
Wow!
Okay, I don't know.
I wish it was a joke. I wish it was just a joke.
But maybe I don't know whenever you joke. There's a little bit of honesty in there, right? I don't know
But hey, how about we play a second haters club? There's only one second haters. I guess there's two. I mean one has more of a
like a
Like a classical music to it the other one is more of a country
Let's play that one real quick and then uh, oh we ever when we gather around the
Pire
Is the alternate version?
Okay, well, I play the alternate version. I played the regular version
You're ready. This is just great. This is one of my shortest songs
Which is like a perfect song. So about last night that was quite a scene it out
Okay, we can talk about it. We'll talk about it. We'll talk about it guys because I don't even saw it
Oh, Psyche's a simp. Psyche's doing all these tactics, he's throwing everything but the
kitchen steak, trying to get acceptance. We'll talk all about it. Let's play the Psyche
Haters Club real quick and then we'll talk all about it, okay? It was quite a scene.
You claim?
Okay, well, you forgive me too. Yeah, you have. But I'm talking about
Bita, no. I mean, basically, I'm at Bita, who I've like, begged for forgiveness.
I beg Christine for forgiveness. She didn't really, because she didn't really forgive me.
She was doing the okey-doke with me, because people were telling me around the scenes
she was still talking mad shit about me while she was pretending to be like, forgiving and stuff.
And then it's like, oh, well, you're not. Yeah. Bita has not forgiven me.
She's never had. I've asked for forgiveness since over a year ago.
Yeah, she hasn't you can give me an example. She said, okay. No, she hasn't
She's just also just like you can say oh, that's because what she lets you on her show
I mean she let me on yesterday and stuff right
She has not think that is we can talk about it. We'll talk about it after the song. Okay, so let me play this song
Psychiatrists
And I didn't do anything to beat it. It was other people and then maybe I did do some stuff along the way
But there was no for forgiveness forgiveness. There was never forgiveness. It was just a carrot in the stick, but I'll play this song
Kristen's mad about crystal, Tony's just full of it
Bronze chicken struts around, but it's looking like a lunatic
Sweet peas gone sour, betas bitter, betty again
Alexander had my back, that's a real one, not pretend
Welcome to the Psyche Hater's Club
Where the jellies gather up, begging for attention
Thirsty and stuck, one club I'm happy I'm not part of
Go hate yourselves
Yeah, go hate yourselves
Bronze chicken, pluck those feathers, toss it in the pan, make it fried.
All that noise you're making can't hide the hurt inside.
They scream for spotlight, but the stage is all mine.
Every hater's just a chorus that proves I'm doing it.
Welcome to the psyche haters club where the jealous gather up begging for attention
Thirsty and stuck, one club I'm happy I'm not part of
Go hate yourselves
Yeah, go hate yourselves
They're lame
As hell like a rerun show taking all their drama, but it's all for show
I'll keep rising
Watch me shine
Haters club stays left behind
Welcome to the Psyche Hater's Club
Where the jealous gather up
Begging for attention
Thirsty and stuck
One club unhappy, I'm not pa-
We have a guest coming up. Let's welcome our guest, our first guest of the night.
Let's give a round, rousing welcome to the beautiful, the illustrious, the uh, is Mr. Clean?
Hey, you're not fully clean unless you're saying that is clean. Hello. Hello, Governor. How are you?
I'm all right. How are you?
well thank you for coming on tonight i know it's like you know it's been a little while and
it's like then i saw you on some other panels and it's like i just want you to know you're going
to be the role of the red carpet is going to be rolled out for you here um you know i have a song
called okay thing that is you remember that song i wrote for you before yep can i find it and play
it for you real quick if you want sure
I think it's actually a good song, it's an important song.
I like the, yeah, it has that like,
oh, you mean the significance of the song.
I meant the music.
I like the house, that 60s.
Oh yeah, thing that is, I'm sorry,
I lost my voice as I was doing the Christina stuff,
but I think you're the only thing that is on YouTube.
We'll see if it comes right up.
Okay, well you are, but the thing that is,
you have been clipped several times.
I'm going through this stuff and let's be on the
Hopefully on the cult of sake page several times. That's interesting. I know what's his face? Jenny has gotten me a couple times today
Jamie has what is she doing? Jenny Jenny clips. Oh, Jenny Jenny clips. Yeah. Yeah
Um, yeah, and Janie Clips, you know, I think like I heard Christine hates her and so that's a plus in her call
Is Janie Clips even a girl? I honestly don't know not that it matters
Well, I don't know either because I was the guy and then Christine kept saying oh, she but then people think it's like Janie
Like a female name and actually I think it means like janitor like a mod. Well, that's what I figured was janitor like, yeah, exactly
Yeah
I mean, that's what I was told.
And so, I mean, it's kind of, hey, by the way,
I want to show you the codex again, but we, we know how,
but you had fun the other day.
Yeah, so, sorry.
The other night when I showed the, when I asked,
was asking, I was like searching the codex
and I was saying, tell me about thing that is,
and stuff like that.
And it said, well, he's like a warlock.
He's like a vampire.
He's a philosopher.
He's like, he sits there in a bunch of chaos.
And that open-minded or something must have some kind of super power of myself.
But it confused me with Mason.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, I'm sorry about that. It's in the grown drums a guitar center and you're 28 years old
It was good content. Like it's funny. I'd like that
Both live with your mom and so I think that was like it just yeah and because of the whole shirt thing
You know, we were always being mentioned together. Yeah
Guys, today I went through, like, you know, so we can talk about Alexander for a second,
Alexander. And I'll play, I'll find the thing that I want. I got nothing really tight.
Okay, okay. Wait, okay. I want to have the Alexander stuff.
Well, she told me last night, she's like, well, you know, she was, she's been kind of negative
at the codex and stuff, right? She was, she's like, oh, this might be a black male tool,
Sam Mann and Bita are, are, are maybe telling him what to put in the codex. And I think she had to
And I think she was impressed because she's like,
she's like, I don't have a problem with your codex.
I think she saw that it was just my show
and basically saw it mainly AI generated,
things up like pull from the transcripts and stuff.
Jenny, I know, I know that Jenny show for janitor
was just slang for chat mods because they sweep up the,
I know.
Yeah, that's what we were saying, right?
Your thing that is considered fire with ice cubes.
You know that can you do that thing that is you are a Canadian right with ice cubes? Is that a compliment?
I don't know what that means. Oh, you mean like I'm cool. Whatever. Oh, what do you because you saw that?
I know I know for maybe the email. I was gonna say a few days. I've been I want to say can't you miss that?
I'm sorry. I've been using it.
But I'm sorry go ahead. No, it's just saying the last few days like I'm on edge these days the quitting smoking has really got me
Yeah, and you've been on it.
Okay, so I wanna say, Kate, you missed that night
that Alexander started timing out people for 10 seconds,
and then we had an IP2 of rage or whatever.
I just wanna explain.
So my life that is the last night,
it's absolutely disgusting the way I spoke.
Okay.
It was I didn't like it either, but I knew that you were trolling like you were playing a joke. I know
And it's like that I mean that word a good thing to do. Oh, I know well
Here I'm desensitized. I think I'm so desensitized from from that work. I get called that word so much and
Also, it was just like once I unmodded everybody and I saw the members there was like one
Out of like a hundred people. Maybe that came that night, right? There's like one member and
I was one last night. Were you drunk or something? What was it? I was high on the endorphins
I was high up from a tattoo. I had to tattoo it. I was just in adrenaline rush
That's all adrenaline rush to say I just talked to all his under mayors and then I talked before that
I talked to peps and Zaya and
But I want to say about the
Know the several reasons case talking about I want to say I did send some
Disturbing messages I say to some people, but I want to say
Yeah, I said if you I said when they found my body look at the list that I put on the on the
my community wall, you know, but you know what because
I get I get certain times and I think I may have gone actually hit of this weed and stuff like that
I get extremely paranoid and I just don't I remember the other night
But have here's what happened the other night when Alex was timing on people for 10 seconds
And you were there thinking this and you kept coming up and you kept saying just
Right you kept saying the same thing over and over and it was yeah, but then it was IP two people came in and they said
You're gonna die tonight. They said you're doxxed. They said you're gonna be swatted tomorrow. We're killing Alexander
We're killing you and we're trolling those right right
But it's like because because I was doing that because I was doing the repetitive thing, right?
And I kind of lit a fire and I got chat going that's why I was doing it being repetitive and all that shit
But I guess she's like going and they did yeah, I didn't mean for them to
That kind of stuff, but and if Kate's still here
I know it was disgusting the way I spoke and yeah, and it was just
YouTube actually deleted that stream
They say you I didn't delete it like I just privated it YouTube deleted it saying it was like and I I was basically trying to take
Myself out of YouTube last night. I was like, let me we get shadow banned. Let me like
We do something and it was like self-destructive. It was like I was just feeling like it was the end
Well, yeah, it's hate speech, but Kate I you call it
This is the self-destructive thing is that you are actively
Trying to make that destruction happen, but also
Yeah, man literally said that word a hundred times does anyone say Sam and you're using a speech and he's not black
It's not the same and you know what I use a a is a hard R and he uses soft age, right?
That's why I saw the same. Yeah, I know the difference come on
I've never used these terms like in my life
It does not pronounce R's K, I mean he's
And I understand the difference.
I understand the difference too.
But here's what I understand.
I get called nigger a lot, okay?
I'll say it again, I don't care.
Do it.
I mean, I mean, dude, don't do it.
There's a different there is not a Kate. That's where the that's where the lie is. That's where the lie is, okay?
Oh, it's okay to say in this context, but it's not okay to say it in this. It's okay
How can two letters change the meaning of something so much unless it's like, you know, you're playing Scrabble or something like that
Okay, okay. Also, I was being
Crash out and it's like and I every time I crash out. I kind of get more and more outrageous. It is Kate. Here's the lie
nigga
Is the same as new they're the same word
You could say they have the same roots. Sure. No one's no one's gonna deny that
They do not mean the same thing and you know that come on come on
Do you think I was saying that I explain that I wasn't saying in a racist way, you know
I don't think you were meeting
how he says that he's like, you know, it means ignorant.
He's like, niggers don't read books and blah, blah, blah.
Right? Or I don't know if he said nigger or nigger, right?
Okay. Listen, listen, listen, Chris.
And that's five because first rock is black, right?
Right. So black people can't use it.
What are you, Michael?
What's his name from the office?
I haven't watched the office. I'm not. That's what he used to be. He wouldn't get in shit for saying
Okay, I love you. Okay. I'm trying to make a point. I know I'm not Chris Rock. I know I'm a Howard sir
I'm not a black man. That's it is 50. I'm not a 75 year old Jewish man. That's a DJ. Okay. I'm saying
That why is it what's right for some is over so why so why and people call me if that you know
You're making the good times argument, right? You know that well good times has an argument because in a context
Even any race will use that what this is a good times argument is like Sam and saying like my brother or myself
The but Sam and saying like my brother everyone's sorry
He calls you a bitch ass nigger. Does he mean it as a compliment dude?
But he says that to you. Do you not hear him say that to you? Who?
Who Sam man? He says it to me. Yeah
Listen psych psych I see Sam and as a very illiterate stupid man, and he can't
I don't but maybe it was also me just like
Fucking crashing onto the extreme. I don't know. It wasn't anything against any race
I know people were defended and everything. I have had a black guy. Fuck me. I mean, is that can I be racist?
A black guy has fucked me. Is that racist?
There's some black guys that like to be called
Slave and stuff during sex. Exactly. Excuse it. Okay, listen to this. Listen to this guys. It's called race play
There's like a race play too. Have you heard of this?
Come on site. You're being ridiculous. You weren't doing a race play. I was doing race. You know, okay. Listen, you took it down
Finish the show at orgasm
It was the best night of my life
Okay, you took it down and like I said, I saw it and I know you weren't actually trying to be offensive to a group of people
I don't think you were being offensive. You were being offensive to people who weren't
I think it's a frol to a black person and then he calls me
He calls me that word and then I call him master and stuff
Sakes
It's happened. It's happened. I'm right. It's okay. Okay. It's okay. You don't have to be tonight and it's okay
No, it's okay. It's fine. I've got people away
Shit if I don't if I don't outwardly say if I don't openly say hey, I'm against what what he's saying right now
People think that I'm fucking agreeing. I someone gave me an hour pass
At least 10 10 African-American people have said I can say it because it's been called to me. Okay, at least
It looks very 20 maybe
Okay, so I have been given the past. Oh, is that there's no such thing in the past?
Well, there's no such thing as like a word really meaning the word, right?
It's like is it in all of our minds? Isn't this all just like fucking like semantics and oh a h and hard er
Isn't it all ridiculous? That's the kind of point. I was trying to prove
Whether I'm driving people away or not I had a hundred people in my chat today. It's not really driving people away. I
Don't think
Okay, well, there's no such thing as a nigger, Kate. It's just a word. It's just a word
In my opinion, it's just a word. The meaning has changed. Is there such a thing as a faggot?
If you you and uh, what's his face good times can get support for this movement
Good luck.
Well, you know whatever.
Is that what you said?
Wait, guys.
That was in Detroit.
Good times.
Okay.
Listen.
Good times.
Let me talk for a second.
Let me make a point.
It's a distinction right now.
You can make it a point.
Sandman is not a black person, okay?
And there's many not black people that are going around saying bitch ass nigga, right? All the time. No one bats an eyelash
No one does anything Bita has said hard ER 50 times people, right? It's a okay
So here's the point I'm making you're good times arguments. I should say bands argument. I'm using it like you know as a bro
It's a cultural thing. It's I just how I was broke doesn't he say it's cool
That's not the argument good times is making
well good times to say exactly the same thing right so if same man can say it with with the
a then good times can say with the word are you're being a bitch kate and i'm and i'm sorry
and i was like i love you kate and i'm sorry but you're being a bitch okay okay
Go ahead on panel. I've got a lot of people without people without people on panel
But I love you Kate and it's like not to say but that saying that kind of thing is trying to be a bit
Trying to hurt me or for someone and you know if you don't ever talk to me again, and you hate me and it's bad
Whatever, but now you're being
Trying to hurt me. Okay, instead of taking your feet. I'm okay. I'm listening to you
I'm trying to explain my side of the story. I didn't mean it in a racial way
Hey, I was just talking to Alexander Mayer's saying I love her
This is like a person I consider my best friend and she's African-American. Do you think I want her?
Okay, my friend, okay
No, I'm not your best friend, don't say that one. Okay, you're good. Oh, you're good on me
They did something erupting me you're good on me meaning you're done with me or
Yeah, I think you're doing you're done and that's fine. Okay, it's fine because
Okay, it's fine go go hang out with beta and you're saying that but it's like
After or if you're good with me
Then you understand my point of view. Okay. Hey, you can go your own way
Like the charisma said that right now remember man, you guys are just having a disagreement right now shut up
You guys sound like me. I love her. I love it. I fucking love her
I fucking like end of my life and I saw she went live and I was like hey
I'm gonna end right now because Kate's awesome and she was such a great friend or she is okay
Come on man. Come on. You guys are just having a disagreement relax
I'm talking to him. I'm telling him. I'm telling him how offensive it was.
I know it was offensive. I was being ridiculous. I know. I understand.
I was trying to take my channel out. I was trying to get shadow banned and stuff like that.
But I was also trying to like say to me, this is okay if you're done with me.
And you know what? A lot of people are done with me. And it's like maybe it's like people that can like.
See, okay, well, let me get in his head.
I'll try to get in your head and stuff, I will.
I see your point of view, you know,
you're with Barry and stuff and it's like,
and you're thinking I'm racist and you're very not racist
and I don't know if you're a mixed race or whatever,
or I kind of assumed you were kind of Irish and stuff,
but whatever race you are, that doesn't matter to me.
I am being gay, I have been so discriminated against,
I've always,
Been with the plight of the black person. I'm very anti-slavery. I mean, I love every race. I'm attracted to most
Mexicans, I think you I think you could say you understand persecution, but I don't think you could say you had this
Okay, I think it is okay. Yes. I'm not black
There's a core there's a correspondence and black gays get at the worst too
I know I know because I've heard these arguments all the time. Okay. I hear these arguments and stuff like that
Okay, she's done with me. It's fine
It's fine, it's fine. Okay, it's all coming down. Listen, I like, I like this. Okay, so Howard Stern,
and I'm not Howard Stern, I'm not Howard Stern, but he would have Daniel Carver on the KKK.
And Howard Stern would also dress up in the KKK outfit in the 80s and stuff like that,
and he would say the heart you are now is culturally completely unacceptable or whatever,
and it's all about unicorns and magic and rainbows and stuff.
I say we're not all that different.
I actually, if I go back into my genealogy,
I have sub-saharan apricot in me.
So is that part of it?
I'm just gonna tell the school back far enough
we have apricot.
Right, is that part of me that I hate?
Am I trying to, like I was telling you to say,
it's not about race.
Just like Chris Rock, and I know I'm not Chris Rock, okay?
But Chris Rock said it means ignorance.
Doesn't, black people use it,
I don't know if black people would mean ignorance, not.
So if not saying I'm him, I'm saying,
here's a perspective from a black man about the word.
where he can maybe say it about a white person.
Okay.
Let's move on to more tangible things, man.
How do you think Alex would react to that?
Alexandra.
I think she might, I think either she would,
either she would maybe, okay.
I mean, if I, listen, I was,
I just got back from her channel, basically.
If I was to hurt her feelings over that,
I would be very regretful.
I would be, I would be sad.
but I didn't get my point across or say it right.
Here's what I think about Alexandra.
I think she's smart enough.
She called Tommy James a nigger.
Dude, answer the fricking question.
How would she feel about your Tyree
with the N word last night?
Okay, so I just said, she called Tommy James a nigger.
She said if this were colonial times, he would be a nigger.
So she said that's about Tommy James.
I'm saying that she would be okay with it,
is what you're saying.
I think she's smart enough to know the troll.
Okay, she I think she's I think she knows I think she knows that
There's I would never call that I'd never call her that word
Ever you know or even think it or anything like that or any black person like not even if you got really really angry at her
I've been really really angry at her. Did I ever use that word to her? I don't know never, okay?
I've been really, I've been as angry as I can be
another human being with her, okay?
Never.
And it's like, now, and then it's like,
this is what they, so, so,
Kay has fallen into Sandman's trap,
where he's like, oh, look at this dude here,
sexy, the Edward, and he's a white person,
and this is gonna be some kind of thing.
I knew I was gonna fall, I knew this would happen, right?
Before it happened.
I'm trying to teach people through maybe
unconventional means and stuff like that.
I'm trying to teach them that words are just words.
And it's like, if you take an offense,
does that mean that you take word to heart?
Then what does that mean?
You know, I disagree with this.
Words are not just words.
They're how we communicate intention to each other.
Sure.
And words are spells.
How do you communicate to each other?
Spells.
Um, Joe Shipley says it and I was joking too, but does anybody like saying whoa, this is a clan member
This guy's racist and he can't say it under time. It's like it's so funny the double standards in the community
There's lots of that but what it's just the way it is, right? It's a troll community
So that means that they don't have to be honest
Do I I
Don't know. I'm just saying am I part of the troll community. I mean
You don't know
Do you know Alexandra considers up the queen of the trolls and perhaps maybe I consider myself the king of the trolls?
Did you know that all right King because we might be troll royalty and we might be
Everyone's so hard because it's like this community kind of deserves it because there's actually mean-spirited evil trolls and okay
I could see that everyone's unbanned and everyone's unmodded.
And so, okay, so also Kate, she might be bad about, also, I unmodded her.
Do you know why I'm modded?
Everybody in chat, every single person, Jamie's Cowboys, who's been my mod for
over two years, or like about two years, a year and a half, every single person.
And I'm the only now person with control, okay?
I don't hate Kate, I love Kate.
Actually, I love Kate.
I think she's like so awesome and charming and funny
and she has this rough side
and she can talk about shit about me and everything.
I'm not gonna go after her, okay?
I respect her, and it's like, even though if I have gone out,
you're not mad about being a model.
Okay, well, that was someone who told me and stuff,
they're probably at troll.
And Kate, you're still here.
So there's part of you that has your ears open, okay?
About to me.
And if you have more to say to me, I'm gonna shut up,
and I'll let you, Kate, come up and talk to me
if you want to, if you can discuss it.
I'll shut up, Kate, I'll.
Yeah.
i'm you hey i really because that's the fact that you're still here and you're not like
fuck him block my channel and all that and started live saying psyche is a fucking you know
horrible person okay i have here's what i was even last night what am i even want to say this
between then i was like this is not about race i'm not trying to hurt anybody's feelings and i
was like this is i'm trying to i'm trying to first of all maybe like change help change the
I understand you weren't intentionally trying to be offensive to a segment of the population.
Okay.
However, the way you were using it could be offensive because listen, you were saying
people who are not us members are end with heart.
You know why?
Because they weren't paid because they couldn't
Okay, also
Hey, you're a mom and I don't know about okay. Okay, but we're talking about impressions. Okay impressions is all about how we take things
Okay, it's all about there can be people I say that to that would just laugh
They can be black people that's his issue and say we'll just laugh, right? I mean everyone has their individual
History with the word that's with all words, right?
Any of parental duties and I want to say Kate and you get in a Kate thing is right
He hasn't said anything wrong. Okay, you haven't said anything wrong today. Like if it's your feelings of
Okay, this is obviously about people who don't donate.
Here's the thing, Kate, and I know I was going to join again, and I did.
I did it today.
I was going to do it last night when I was playing about the non-donators.
I am basically like, if I was, okay, this is IP2 crowd.
They want to watch me die basically. They would they'd be they're trying to watch you die
Sometimes they do it by starving you sometimes they do it by feeding you the wrong things
Okay, there's there's a certain couple ways they do it
They decided to go at me
What that kills me the burping kills me. I'm sorry. I've been drinking alcohol. It's just like a fart
I know it just makes me laugh. I don't know. Okay. Yeah, well, I'm not gonna for okay
You might, you might, but yours are silent and dead.
I can just tell by that look on your face sometimes.
Give us, give us, okay.
I didn't fart, no, no, no.
I know, okay, okay.
No, I would lean and.
I've seen you lean before, and then people,
why wouldn't you stand up
when people were asking you to stand up?
When?
Who was asking me to stand up?
Okay, and Kate, someone asked you to stand up before.
I know you're bothering Kate, and it's like, and I know,
your racial history or about your history with people of different races and stuff.
All I can say is that I love people of all races and I'm not racist.
Like I know I'm not that's why I feel like I kind of say it almost because it's like
I'm so beyond racism or hate of any any pity because of their skin color.
If I was calling white people, it's been probably mainly white people. That's what I was compensating when you do it like that
I am so against race. I don't see color or anything. That's fucking I don't I really don't because I
You can recognize the the differences you don't know, but I wasn't saying a racial way
I would have said I wasn't saying in a racial way
I wasn't mean and I said that I didn't mean it in a racial way. I was saying
I've said that go on, right? Okay. And if we say that then I mean that takes care of it basically because it's like
The only problem would be if I was trying to say it against this specific race for hate against their grace and it wasn't about that
It was saying
Hey, I'm here
Every fucking day
I have all these people making, like you say,
oh, mom, me, mommy, and I'm not saying the gutter.
Like I had a lot of people in the shout out donated
and stuff like that.
I know what you were doing.
You were doing it to rebel against all the noise
that's been brought against you,
especially about the other night with the whole,
the whole end thing with going on with the other stream
and all that stuff, okay?
So I understand exactly why you did it,
but it wasn't cool.
I'm glad you took it down.
I didn't take it down, it was taken down by YouTube.
YouTube deleted it, they said it was hate series.
Whatever, yeah, I mean, it wasn't quite it.
You know what, that was trying to do that.
You know why I said it over and over again?
Besides just being drunk and stupid?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I get it.
I was trying to like, my channel's like this close
to deletion and it's like, if I,
if my channel gets taken down, I'd rather,
rather I do it, than have someone to blame
and be angry at the rest of my life that does it.
That makes sense at all making it happen. I understand what you're saying, but you're making it. You're actively
I just said I was trying to do that I said I was trying to say instead of just doing your thing
And if your thing results in the channel going down, that's one thing
But being active to actually make it go down. That's that's just that's nonsense. That's ridiculous
see me in one minute hi chat to anyone who's come in since last time i said hi chat
how would he sing he's like where's he talking now i'm not now come my formal apology here's my
formal apology this is my coup this is the coup de gras or whatever it is here's the coup de gras
hey i'm a fucking idiot i'm a fucking guys look at me i'm a mess
I mean, I'm a mess. I've been through fucking trauma. I've been through all this shit. I'm not
I'm not. Here's a song. I'm not a perfect person. I'm sorry. There's many things I wish I didn't do,
but I continue learning. And so here's what I have to say to you. I've got one thing to say
I found a reason for me to change who I used to be a reason to start over new
and the reason is you hear one more thing to say I never meant to hurt you it's something that
Now I need to look at the lyrics, I'm sorry.
Then you can say something, I'm gonna sing the rest of it.
I can't remember everything, I'm so drunk, hold on.
I'm gonna get the lyrics for it.
Why am I always on panel when someone starts singing badly?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, I'm sorry that I hurt you.
It's something I must live with every day and all the pain I put you through.
i wish that i could take it all away and be the one i'm getting chills i'm sorry i'm getting goosebumps
and be the one that catches all your tears that's why i need you to hear i found a reason for me
to change you i used to be the reason to start over new and the reason is you that's all i have to say
Who's I kind of forgot what the if I was who was saying who was saying and it's called the reason and the video is so great
It's really who is that dedicated to like why were you singing that?
That's it for everybody. Oh
For you guys, especially
My my little bald friends here, and I'm not trying to be gay, but I want to like rub your head a little bit and say
No, I'm not gonna be gay. I'm gonna give you a term. Honestly, if I were a lucky term
I was trying to say I want to like give you a little rub on your lucky
Mr. Clean, Mr. Clean, and I want to give you a pat on your butt on your back
Why are you making that face at me?
Listen, if we're on the same team playing sports or whatever and I were wearing big
bulky like hockey pants with lots of padding, I would let you smack my butt with the hockey
stick.
Hey, see that is.
Can I?
That is.
Okay.
First of all, may I join your hockey team and second of all, can I second of all, hockey
stick and then one time?
No.
I didn't want that.
Okay.
I'm embarrassed.
Now I'm embarrassed.
Thanks a lot
Okay
Hey, you know who says that like that beta you're picking up beat his habits now
What is it?
You said okay, okay, the beta does. Oh, yeah, you think I'm picking up her mannerisms
Little bit. Yeah
You're watching too much beta. She is on a lot
Maybe
I
Know okay, okay. I'm assuming that channel
I know I am and I want ever scrubs easy cameras on at a great time there tonight
And I'm gonna leave it on until he ends and stuff and thank you kid for letting me know
Thank you for letting me know okay. Hey if Kate hated me, would she let me know that?
I don't think she hates you. Like I said, you guys have a different opinion.
I don't know, do I think that Kate thinks I'm a bad person? Because I was, I think she's not even saying that.
She watches the stream, she's gonna be saying that.
At the end of the day, have I done something so unforgivable? I'm not worth forgiveness.
Are you talking to me still?
Yeah.
Or are you still talking?
Yeah, it's Chad too, and Kate, and whoever's listening.
At the end of the day, this is 40 diamonds talking now.
I'm channeling her spirit.
I hope she's still alive.
OK.
At the end of the day, I'm going to go to the blade right now.
OK, hold on a second.
Oh, I'm going to do it somewhere else.
Oh my god, I just felt it.
OK, no.
I'm so sorry. Did you ever see the flirty dive when she did a somersault and she fell? No, I heard about it
I don't want to see it. I've heard about though. Hey, it is I
Haven't laughed so hard. I don't think in my entire life when I saw you don't want to see that
You don't want to laugh as hard in your entire life
as you can at somebody drinking.
I don't know that, no.
I just saw a smile in your, I just saw a smile.
I don't wanna see it.
Yeah, I saw it, I saw it, I saw it.
Yo, did you see that smile on his face
when he couldn't stop,
he couldn't tell from like almost smiling?
I love that, I love that about you.
That it's like, you're so unreadable,
you're so calm, you see that?
And there's like a little,
This is it was half a second is a micro expression and you were like there's a little half of your smile went up
Yeah, you know, I laugh a lot at situations like I find things funny. I find like odd
Funny guys guys
Laughing me that
Call me that word. I mean, it's like it's just a pile on me
I think the worst circumstance, but if somebody phrases something in a way that I just find funny
I'll fucking go
I want to say everyone's unmodded. There's not one mod except and I'm not even modded. I don't think in my chat
I think I think maybe nightbot is modded and I have a I have made a robot too and so I just want to say guys
Yes, I'm not perfect. Yes. I'll say outrageous
horrible horrible things and I want to see after the after the smoke clears
Who's gonna be there? Give me a hug
And last night I'm a hug. Are you gonna be giving me because I'm entertained you wouldn't give me a hug
Well virtual hug. Yeah, okay. That's more than Alexander dick
I mean, but it's okay. I was not gonna the guy that's not just about Alexandra and I know but I said Alexander
I said, can I have a hug?
She said no. Yeah. Yeah, I say have a high five
And you know, she said no, that's right. I said I said you what I said next
Can I have me can I have a?
Smile oh, can I give you a smile and she said yes. Yeah, that's right that I remember
Or is it gonna have a smile and then she gave me a smirk like
And I didn't involve any physical contact right you didn't have to actually touch
The virtual hug or to the virtual high five involving virtual you said
Oh
It was a it's virtual this is virtual. This is the point. This is just virtual
That's the point. I'm trying to make I'm playing with you. But listen what I said in chat
Before about the one thing that I take exception to is that you because I asked you last night when it was done
What did you take away from that thing with Alexander?
And you said, she forgave me.
She's the only one that's ever forgiven me.
I said, and I'm like, no, man, that's not true.
Oh, no, no, you're wrong.
Here's why I can't talk just for a minute.
Just let me talk for a minute, okay?
Just let me talk for a minute.
I said, I'm sorry.
I said, and she said, I'm not gonna apologize to you.
And I said, no, no, no, I'm apologizing to you.
You did nothing wrong.
I take full responsibility.
I'm sorry.
I said, you don't owe me an apology.
I said, it's all my fault.
And I said, listen, this is what I said.
And I told her what I'm sorry for.
And I said, do you accept my apology?
And she said, yes.
And that was it.
That was it.
Okay.
I apologize to Bita a million times.
Beat a house
Right, right, let me let me finish okay at the beginning she was forgiving you psych but like I said
Forgive me because the same thing keeps saying it is were you here last April?
Maybe I don't remember. No, you are not. You are here. Maybe maybe in chat. I wasn't on
See you interact with us. Okay
The first time I actually you registered my mind is you remember and stuff the first time I registered my mind was when spunky said
Ban thing that is because this thing that is guy. Yeah, I remember that. Yeah, you remember that when I started getting active with coming on
I'm never coming to your chat again, Psyche, and I'm done with you.
I say that, so what?
So what?
I say things I don't mean either.
I say things stupid things.
I have a trauma hurt.
The ignorance.
I say stupid things stupid.
Whatever we say or whatever certain people say has to be taken literally and make-
Exactly!
That's my point!
But other people can just say things as jokes.
It's just a while.
I didn't mean it.
It was just a joke.
I was joking.
For people that they hate, it's like, oh, no, no, everything you say is absolute.
Exactly.
It's such hypocrisy.
It's fucking ridiculous.
Yes.
He got it exactly.
Exactly what I was trying to say.
That was the point of the whole thing, then it is, you got it brilliantly.
Thank you for putting it at work.
I long recognize this shit, man.
The only point I was trying to make is exactly what you just said that's the only point I was trying to make. Okay
But are you next to hold me and say it is something wrong?
Why are your eyes going back and forth? I'm not sure exactly what
Oh my god. Okay. Okay. This is called talking about the apology. That's why I got him guys. Okay. I got it
No, I just don't understand what you mean here
Okay, so you're just talking about that hypocrisy and stuff and how some rules are applied to others over the place
Yeah, I'm not pointing it
Now isn't it true isn't it true Chanel isn't it isn't it?
He's so I mean he but that's the point I was and maybe I made the point in the wrong way
But that is the point I was trying to make whatever he came out of his mouth those words you put it the perfect way
That's what I was trying to say
I didn't maybe say it the right way,
I maybe said it in an offensive way,
and maybe an attention-getting way, attention-getting.
Hey, hey, hey.
Yeah, I'm ready to get attention. I'm gonna get your attention not get attention get your attention
I don't take what people say on here
Commenting on real life matters like if they start talking about your real life shit, then I start taking that seriously
I don't think people
Threatening real life stuff. Okay. That's not a choice
was I that's a threat. It's a threat. It's not a threat.
I was I threatening. I don't say that being a personal real
life. So with a person or is that being very general and
trying to make the point that you're making me a word and
hear you man. I can't. I can't turn it up too loud. My
brother's next door. Sorry. What's your brother's name? The
thing that isn't? I'm not going to tell you his name.
I mean this I'm not asking you to tell me his real name. I said it's the same thing that isn't
Thing that is too. I don't know. Okay. That's what you're supposed to say
Oh my god thing that also is I don't know. Oh, okay, whatever. Is he in the chat right now?
No, no, he doesn't that wasn't him when you were not dancing with your shirts off it show you showing your butt
Oh, no, no you and that video my brother is like 18 years younger than me
Okay. Now, like, he was, he was, he was, he was, now, now, because he is like 30 years
old or something like that. I'm sorry. I'm perfect. He's four. I'm going to start 40.
Well, I'm five years older. And so, okay, if you have a question about you or a question
for you, when I talk to Benny, I talk to Benny, you know, Benny, when I talk to him,
Everyone's like, he's a child.
How dare you talk to him and stuff like that?
I don't know.
Let me just say, let me just finish.
Not even flirting or anything, just being a bro.
Because I'm gay, it's a different, okay?
But when Paige, who's I believe 38, 39,
they're trading Snapchat, live, Instagram numbers,
flirting, is that wrong?
Dude, are you complaining that that there's uh, no, no, no, not at all
Is Paige getting any shit shit for talking to Betty and do I get shit? No, I think Paige raised eyebrows like
Like why is she give her my is it her Instagram and her snap? Yeah, that's what I'm saying
I think she raised eyebrows like really you're into this guy like why are you?
Why is she judging him, you know, he's like to say almost my same age and why, why, why
was it you?
But I'm not interested in him sexually and she might be.
Will you just let me explain this because you're gay because he's not that young.
People automatically go to that stupid town.
A woman does it.
The guys are stuck.
Because they, they're trying to hurt you, psych, they're trying to get you.
Yes, yes, he got it again.
He gets it.
Why are they trying to hurt me?
Some people just don't like you other people just want to see you freak out because it's funny
Die, how about see me die?
How about what see me die? I
Don't think so
That didn't sound very convincing I mean no one that I know is no in a unit. Okay, okay
No, no one no one that that I that I
Talked to her whatever is trying to do that man. If you're talking about some
What you know to said you're Merlin you're Merlin
Why do you smile like that? Because you are in Merlin.
Because I'm in Merlin.
I'm in Merlin, and you I'm in Maryland.
I'm in Maryland, okay?
Oh my God.
No, don't be in Maryland.
Don't. What are you doing?
Hey, dude, what the hell are you doing?
I have to wear this one in my dress.
What are you, what are you hiding?
Why was wrong?
What the fuck, man?
What's wrong?
You don't like the American flag?
Jesus, now when there's balls behind it, no.
My balls are just coming through my legs.
Get off the screen. Get out of here. Stop it.
I'm so sorry.
Oh my God.
Oh, did I just do that?
I think I thought we were on the phone privately. What was I'm sure any at NYC fucking left that he's probably clipped it
And he's played it. He's probably stroking to it right now. That's gonna be oh look at psyche hitting on this straight man
And are we really that offended?
Or did you almost have it?
I just I don't
I mean just pull my pants, okay
Fucking guy.
You laughed! You laughed!
You laughed, guys. Guys, you're gonna help it.
You're gonna help laughing.
Guys, it's just funny. Some things are just funny.
I'm not offended, like I said.
I don't...
I'm not offended.
I thought you were laughing.
But I don't want to, like, look at fucking
cock and balls either, man, or ass.
Or male's ass, you know?
It's not a male's ass.
Fuck you, fucker.
Okay, I'm so sorry. Okay. No, that's right. Never mind. Never mind. Okay. Fuck it. Fuck
Hold on. I'm gonna pull back my belt. I'm so sorry. I am so sorry guys guys
Canadian flag speed oh, yeah, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I
Did something bad. I did a bad bad thing. I said words
I showed my speedo with my maybe maybe a little bit of my nuts that came there's
there's enough people hate watching right now this is 20 people there's a
hundred billion Samans I was at Samans for literally five hours waiting to get
on
And then, after this song, after this song,
oh, this mumble rap, it sounds like retarded people
trying to learn how to speak through these songs.
They're the worst.
I was like, please, you start the content.
And then I finally get on panel.
Finally, after hours, I go on panel.
30 seconds to one minute.
I can't even say shillulu because I have to be rich hearted to say it like he says I get it has to be like
I'm kicked off.
And then he's like, oh, well, I'm gonna play tribute tomorrow
Against J1 and beta. I'm like, are you smarter than a kindergartner guys? No
I said, I mean, I'm at least smarter than a fifth,
I think I'm smarter than a fifth grader.
I think I am.
They're not even smarter than a kindergartner.
And these is what everyone, they want everyone,
because everyone, like not everyone,
but it's like a lot of people, that's their thing.
Who's challenging J1 and Beta?
What are you talking about?
Sam-Man, he's gonna do the tri-
Sam-Man was challenging J1 and Beta to a-
Trivia.
To trivia.
Yeah, why?
Because he thinks they're dumber than him.
I don't care.
On the in preschool and kindergarten. I don't think J1 is dumb. I don't know but they assume he is because socially awkward
But he's not exactly. Oh my god. Okay. I love it. I love this and they think because if you're socially because all they are is socially
adept
Right? They're socially adept.
They're able to get these huge numbers and all these people that like them and have this person out.
And then Poojee would,
Oh, be this cute.
But he probably reads like a, like a mourn piece in the morning.
You know, by the time he finishes his coffee and then he's like,
Oh, be this cute.
Because he probably hasn't had sex in a while.
And he wants to be part of things too.
Right?
We love J1 and stuff. I'm not trying to put down J1 and stuff.
Yeah, I like J1. I'm sorry, Samantha.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I am not explaining.
So what happened? Did they end up playing trivia?
Well, he said it was a 24 hour stream or something.
I don't know. I don't know. Hey, in the guy.
And now look at the chat, too.
Remember how I was saying no one's a member?
Look who's here. Member KZXXO, reality and see.
Pit I pillow by the Chanel here last night Samantha was here last night, but the other ones weren't
Chanel was for a bet
And they've now they've come to help me out and
That's a and I would never call them the n-word I promise
The n-word I call them I call them greenies and if I call them greenies
Oh, that's offensive. He's calling me a color by the colors name. It just means your name is green
It's like not trying to be racist.
I was saying your name is N-I-G-G-E-R because your name is black and you're not a superhero.
We've gone like way off track here, okay?
My thing, like I said, my thing was that you have been given forgiveness by others as well.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not saying you're still being forgiven now, I'm not saying you still are.
I'm saying you have been.
And that's that's the only fucking quam I have with this is because you said she's the only one that's ever forgiving you and that's not true
It hasn't forgiven me. She forgave me. She would have forgiven me
And that would be it but no it's like oh if you reached this slammer if you reached it
Oh, no, man. No
No, no, no
No, no
Okay. Okay. I'm sure her, I'm sure her first forget was absolutely. I'm sure it was. I,
I don't think it had conditioned to it, but. Oh, you don't think so?
Something went wrong. I don't think. No, I don't know exactly.
It's Dr. Phil. Your bald is him. Tell me what went wrong.
I'll just smile right there. What went wrong? Tell me. Why are you smiling?
Well, tell me what I did wrong
Perfectly, oh, it's happened that led to you asking for forgiveness again. And then
Let's see you ask
Again, this you and beta
Huh, what happens with you and beta that you're in there you're upset with her
I quit smoking. That's all that happened between me. I was pissed at somebody else and I took it out on her
Although some of it is
Is also
Human fish on this I overdid it with her
One and only
I'm a human modern Marvel. Yes
Thank you for letting me on your stream I'm gonna go get a coffee the one and only human fish
I would ask this guy this guy thing that is thing that is go to your doctor and get your t-levels checked
Say I'm not messing with you
Go get your t-levels check thing. It's right about that age, buddy. I'll ask you one favor. I think you might need some assistance
Can you shop one second? Can you say the enemy with a heart all right now?
Well, if you ask me to do something then I would expect you to not okay get out of here
I mean, you're not gonna, you're not gonna play along and make my, help me make one point.
You're useless to me.
You nigger.
Fuck, I did it again.
God damn it.
God.
Gosh darn it.
Wow, this is awkward now.
Now it's turned into something awkward.
Meaning you take the message once again
Please stop now
My god
Yeah, I mean trying this I'll just say ask him a question get him get him
Oh my gosh, hold on one second.
Hey, babe, um, maybe I don't, I don't, I'm a little bit, I'm a little bit,
we have a guest on the show. Let's welcome Q45 and uh, sick back.
But what are you doing?
Sick, can you say?
Let's take a shot.
I love it. I love it. Can you say please more shots? Can you say you say, can you say please say and then say repeat?
What you want me to say? Can you do that? It's a don't talk and say this ain't your panel. Why are you telling people what to do?
I wasn't asking you fucking faggot
Want me to say something could you ask please say you want to command psyche?
What is it that you want me to say and I'll say it
I'm going to say my name is Sig. I have a really asking you because like you said, you're not the host. You're right
You're not the host so I wasn't really asking you. I appreciate your input
What I need to what
Sticks up talking at people my pequito, you know what?
That's fair criticism. That's fair criticism. The thing is people like Q45 you do kind of have to talk out
You do kind of have to talk at these people
Yeah, you're a bitch ass nigga
That's the only real angle that you can come in at with because that's the same angle that they're coming at you with
You can't even put your dick at an angle. Yeah, and it's gonna be something where you're gonna have to talk at it
Q45 only engages in very shallow
Conversations are really shallow and there's a much thought behind it
I'm willing to engage in that sort of conversation, but it seems to be more you're a whore
Are desirable to engage in talking people press press one in the thing
I think that you're really trying to get at press one in the chat if you like like oh sick
No, I do I talk at people but here's the thing. I'm good at talking at people
You're right. I talk at people, but I'm actually good at it
That's why people like be to just kick me out people like Sam and people like be
They kick me out because I'm so good at talking at people and just stating things
That they don't have anything to refute. They don't have anything to to say
They can't negate anything that I'm saying or at least they're not proficient enough themselves
Oh my god, nobody cares about your fake fucking
You have this like
Oh, I have like a good vocabulary even though I'm sure the thing that is what's the last time
Nobody gives a fuck about you you're short you have a small penis and you're I'm just gonna ignore this guy in the middle
Talk is letting you know I'm asking you letting you know that this question. I
Take a year in your 40s
We're asking
What's the last time you got your t-levels checked? Oh my god, I know that I ever have the fuck do you care you'd never have
Jesus Christ, thank you psyche if that was you
Yeah
But as you know Q oh
Yeah, he hates me
Hey, man, I was totally fine with you and then I saw you in chat fucking shit talking me
So here's the thing I started with you the thing you got to understand about me, bro
Uh, I talk shit, but like I'm not a part of this like drama
Panel shit like I don't really care at the end of the day. I just I'm just here to chill like I always say
I'm a banter motherfucker. I just get a drama. I just get drunk and join streams. It's really not that deep
All I said to you is that you're a fake good times,
which you still are the fake good times.
I'm the fake good times?
Yeah.
You're the, the team of good times.
How am I even close to,
but how am I even close to good times?
Like I look at that.
You're like good times if he wasn't such a drunk.
Like he'd like a semi-drunk.
I rarely drink honestly.
I mean, I had wine today, it's Easter, but.
I know you've had wine,
I can fucking hear it from here.
You're an ass like I am drinking coffee, right? I've been drinking like three hours or so
Are you smoking something I know you're I know you're Canadian you smoking weed or something
Weed yeah, I just recently quit smoking cigarettes. So yeah, just weed
So you don't you didn't go on the vapes or nothing you just quit cold turkey cigarettes
I try that's harder. That's honestly like harder than heroin like that shit is terrible
Nicotine is such a fucker
Maybe but you know when you get
You know you get to a point where it's like, okay, I got to do it right now
This has to happen and that's pretty much what it was
Did you get like a medical notice or something like they said you had to fucking quit that shit? No, you know
Doctors will always tell you you have to quit it doesn't matter. Oh, of course. Yeah, but even if you're 22 and in perfect health
They're gonna tell you to stop smoking. But yeah, something was found that
Caused me like immediately. Okay. Well, I'm quitting today
So hopefully whatever it was, it's not from Iran
It looks like it's okay, I'm
99.99% sure at this point that it's okay
The doctor even thinks so but the final result is not gonna be for a few weeks, but I'm pretty sure it's okay
I mean even if it's something at least that you know, they probably caught it early, you know, I mean like yeah
I don't even think it is it like the doctor the doctor had a good look at it the other day like a really good look at it and he says it
Yeah, but those are Canadian doctors
In any case, the final result that that'll say whether it is or not is not for a few
weeks.
You gotta come down here and get an opinion from an American doctor and pay like $3,000.
That's how you know.
It cost me, I had to pay for it, the consultation, it was $200, $194 Canadian.
I mean, that's not bad. That's like a, that's like a visit to a MedExpress. So like a quick, you know, MedExpress is like, you know, where it's like a clinic, you know, it's in a hospital, you know, you just walk in there. If you have like, they have doctors that'll see you quickly.
It's not, you know, it's not like a big hospital or nothing, you know what I mean? It's like urgent care. It's like a, it's like a, it's like a little urgent care.
Here they're called everybody who says MedExpress is like the the company that does most of them here
That's why I call them fucking MedExpresses. Yeah
All the Americans in the chat, I'm sure they know about the goddamn MedExpress
So for this kind of $90 for a physical
First up with specialists. Yeah, you pay you pay for the visits and all that stuff
But if it's just a regular family doctor or a specialist
related to something like
Like gastrointestinal or something like that. I mean you don't pay for those
This gay guy fucking Nick Johnson in the chat said,
I quit smoking cigarettes back in 2001.
Yeah, that's when the first fucking Fast and Furious movie came out, you old ass.
That's good though, good for you man, if you haven't picked it up since.
No, you need to keep smoking cigarettes.
That's maybe that's your problem, Nick.
You start smoking cigarettes and then all of a sudden you get all retarded.
Maybe you need to start smoking cigarettes again and you'll be normal.
What a psycho.
Look, he's in chat, fucker.
He's probably walking to McDonald's or something.
Never heard of MedExpress?
You never heard of MedExpress?
Kate, what the fuck?
You call yourself an American?
That's crazy.
There's MedExpress and there's also Concentra too.
Concentra's like the other big fucking...
Urgent care clinic
And then how but really they don't do anything in there though like you you go there and you pay a bunch of money and like
They can't tell you nothing like it's not a hospital like what the fuck are they gonna do they can't they can't prescribe you anything
Right, they tell you to go to emergency if it's serious exactly, but yeah, exactly. Yeah. Oh, it looks really bad
I think you should go to the hospital. That's like their whole job
So what are you guys kiss soon? You know what?
His lips do look pretty juicy
I might I might I might Jenny you flex and I'll kiss him on his big bald head
About that reminds me what what sick said sick said he assumes. I'm in my 40s
Right, which is great because I'm almost 60. I'm 58
You're almost 60. Yeah
And he looked pretty good for almost 60. I mean I would say that you were like I mean
I'm sure you've seen good times before. Yeah, that motherfuckers only like 44. He was born in like 81
I know and he looks older than me
Yeah, he drank a lot of hard liquor
He didn't just stick it to the beers
It's been, it's my whole life, my family,
we've always looked younger,
especially on my mother's side, we look younger.
Everyone looks young, you just end up going bald early.
Yeah, that's on my mother's side for sure, the going bald.
So they always say that, and I'm not sure,
cause you know, all of my father's side of the family,
like they all end up going bald,
which most men do anyway.
But then my mother's side of the family,
they, all the men have hair.
My dad just recently, recently passed away and he had full head of hair right to the end.
But was he like 80?
Yeah, he was like 87, something like that.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
I hope I can fucking keep my hair for that long.
I mean, I'm sure you I'm sure you see when I look like I have a big fucking man bun
Yeah, it wasn't like he was he was 25 like with the front
You know the hairline to here, but he had like, you know full hair
It is not I mean the older you get of the older you get
The your hairline matures, you know, I mean it doesn't it's not necessarily like gets pushed back
But like here wait I could fucking
I'll show you like how my fucking hairline is like I've seen yours your hairline is pretty much
You have like that
It's not like receding but it it matures over time with your forehead
You know what I mean, right? But the balding usually happens from the back right from the crown on the crown. Yeah, yeah
Well, some people some people
They start balding here then the crown some people start balding at the crown first then they start with their hairline receding
It just depends. I guess that's the genetic shit or whatever, but if I ever start all when I start losing my hair, I'm going to be very upset about it.
You in your 30s now?
No, I'm 28. I just turned 28.
Okay. I would probably in a few years from your age is when I started when it started moving.
Like when it started noticing and started seeing hairs on on the pillow and that that's when
That's the see I'm paying attention to it like so especially since I'm on panels and stuff
So I will have like an archive of you know
I'll be able to look at my hairline from past times from being a streamer and shit
So I definitely do pay attention to it
When I do lose my hair though, I will I will accept it
I will shave it all off and I will have a really mean-ass fucking hat collection
That's what I did. I mean, I don't wear hats, but I just I mean I haven't shaved for a little while now
But I usually just shave it off and I'm lucky. Yeah, but you have a good shape head for being bald
I I don't think I do my my head shape is not good for being bald. It's gonna look like a fucking alien
I'm gonna look like I'm fucking phoning home
Then you better start saving for plugs man. I don't know what to tell you. No, no, that's what I said
I'm just gonna buy a bunch of baseball hats. That's it, you know
Just gonna have to rock the baseball hat life
I had a buddy who did that wore baseball hats all the time. I think even in the bedroom like I think
That's why I said if I go bald. I'm just gonna I'm just gonna wear baseball hats. Fuck it
You know, I'll just have a mean ass collection of some nice ass baseball hats
Oh, well
My dentist name Chanel
My dentist they're they're Arabs man. It's a it's a little it's a family thing
Shilobi or question for Q45 when is the correct time to call someone the n-word? See that's a that's a good question
I think that um, I think it goes by a feeling you know what I mean?
There is no one any good time. You just it's just something that you feel you know
Like when you call somebody a fucking dirty
Oh, I guess I didn't say it. Um, you know, you just got to feel it in your in your bones. That's all I
Shout out to that person that asked that question
That was a gangster ass question
Never queue, okay, I'm sorry Kate. I know
Know you love black people and stuff. I don't mean to offend you
But I really just say the n-word because other people get offended by it
If other people got offended by the word waffle, I would say that all the time, too
It just so happens that the n-word
offends the shit out of people
I'm far from a skinhead
I'm so not racist. I don't even see color.
No, you're like a crackhead Jason Statham.
Yeah, yeah, except the crack. I don't do crack.
Except the crack.
I just smoke weed, but sure, I like Statham. I don't mind being compared to him. That's fine.
Except he's talented man. He's got talent man. He's got the martial arts
But he plays every he plays the same character in like all this fucking movies
You know what I mean? Like he's like it's like I love Denzel Washington, too
But Denzel Washington plays like the same character in almost all of his movies, you know, they just have different names, right?
Yeah, there are those typecasts guys. Yeah, Statham is one of them like it
It's almost like every time I see Denzel in the movie. He's playing a version of himself in training day
You know what I mean? Like he's playing like a version of that character in training day. I
Like same with Jason Statham. I always feel like he's playing a version of himself in the transporter. You know what I mean?
Oh, really? What about before that in, uh, what was that?
That's how I remember him from the transporter originally.
Like the first trans, but driving the fucking Audi with the V10.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I like those movies, especially the first transporter.
That was cool.
He was sick as fuck.
He was in the, um...
That's what made him, that was like his, uh, that was like his massive furious, you know?
That was, he, that's how, that's like, that's, uh, how I...
I knew him from being famed like a famous person was from the transporter movies before that. I didn't even know who the fuck he was
There was that movie. Do you remember what with where Brad Pitt played like an Indian gypsy boxer?
Brad Pitt played an Indian gypsy I'm sorry Irish Irish. I don't know why I said Indian Irish
Fight Club
No before what the hell is it called? Come on someone in chat. I cannot remember it right now for the life of me
By the same director that did the lock stock and two smoking barrels
That they did the show
No, yeah, that's what it was called. I've never seen that movie actually. I know what you're talking about
I've never actually watched that movie. It's good man. It's pretty good
It's got that signature
The director I can't remember his name. It's got his signature touch where there's a whole bunch of stories independent stories
And they all kind of come together. It's pretty good. I
Love movies from like the early 2000s. I don't know there's something about like that
Shit from like 2000 to like 2004
Shit from that point is like is hilarious and good at the same time like I've ever seen like Jason X
Oh yeah, we said that's the one where he goes to space or something like that?
Yeah, yeah, it takes place on a spaceship.
Yeah, that was so bad, it's one of those, it's so bad, it's funny movies.
Exactly, I love, it came out like 02 or 03 or something, it's just so hilarious.
Cause like for some reason they started making like Jason movies, like remember Jason is in Manhattan, then Jason X was in space, like they just took Jason and did whatever with them.
Like they milked that shit dry.
And then they started having to do outlandish deaths, right?
Because you had those final destination movies, it just started.
Where they oh, yeah, we're desolated Jason and and all those kinds of movies started having like weird deaths where they had to be all
Contrived and all that shit
Right. Yeah, cuz they were like competing to who is gonna be like the goriest. Yeah, all that kind of crap. I
Don't really care for those. I don't really care for Jason and
And Freddy Krueger, but I do love Halloween and Michael Myers that shit
My favorite actually like the Jason Friday 13th more than Halloween
But the first Friday the 13th isn't even really about Jason, you know, I mean like
It's like yeah, it's about his mother and then he comes in it
Like he's kind of there at the end and he like jumps out of the pond and shit
So it doesn't it doesn't really become about Jason until like the second or third one, right?
The third one is when I was old enough
I think I was old enough to go see it in theater.
That was the one where it was 3D at first release.
And that was pretty cool at the time.
I'll tell you what, though, that fucking the ending scene of the first
Friday, the 13th is fucking scary when they're out in the boat
and then he just like pops up and fucking grabs him.
That shit is scary as fuck.
It was a good movie, right?
You had that final jump scare that got you.
Yeah, honestly, I think that the first out of the Friday the 13th movies
I think the first one is the best one because it like
It lays out everything and it's not really about Jason and the there's no hockey mask or any of that shit
There's just right. I think I don't even think he even gets the hockey mask until like the third movie. Yeah
He had the bag remember the second movie had the bag. Yeah, he was walking a bag on his head
It was like a it was like a it was like a potato sack or some shit
Yeah, I mean right it was a third and right at the end
I think of the second or right at the beginning of the third he picks up
Yes
Yes, the hockey goalie mask and that's crazy that he's like remembered for that and it wasn't even a part of them first like the original movies like everybody remembers him with the mask on though and he's like that never even happened for a long time.
I know it's one of those things where you get say you could probably get someone with that in that.
What's called where you miss remember things from the past.
Oh, Mandela.
Mandela.
And it's like Michael Myers like the first Michael the first Halloween movie Michael Myers already had his mask
Like he was already he was already that guy with the mask and the fucking butcher knife and shit
Like he was already there Jason. It was like a progression of events. I think what I liked about Friday 13th
More was it had a little more of a supernatural thing to it because Jason wasn't like really alive. He was just like a
He's like an entity like he can like take control of other bodies like he didn't you can't kill him
Michael Myers you can't really kill him either. I mean that motherfucker
But at the beginning like the first movie he was just a psychopath, right? He wasn't like oh, yeah
He was yeah, yeah, he was just a psycho who killed his sister and her boyfriend and shit and
Went off on the yeah, he was like he was a little kid who went on a killing spree and uh
Originally that was like you know his his origin story, but he
He's not the same thing as Jason where Jason is literally like not even a human
He just like takes on human bodies like that motherfucker will die
You could burn him alive and he'll just like respawn back as some other human
He came back from rotting at the bottom of the lake, man. I mean
Because he's not a person he's literally he's just he's like a he's like a demon that will like take control of somebody's body almost
It's fucking wild and obviously ready like
like freddy you can't kill him because he does he freddy doesn't even technically exist in the
real world he's a dream but there's no reasoning with these with those types right they're not
human there there's absolutely no way that they're not going to have any grace any uh uh pity nothing
right whereas a human there's the possibility
Yeah, I mean
Out of those three there. No, they're yeah, there's no humanism like none of them portray it
Like even Michael Myers Jason like they don't have any sort of human traits to them
They just are like stone cold fucking killers. They'll kill anything. That's in their path
What do you mean they were both real who do you mean?
psych
Yeah, Jason is I mean Michael Meyer and Jason they both technically lived as human beings
So yeah, technically they were real in the story like real human beings
But then as the movies go as the movies go on Jason ain't really a real person
Michael Myers it it depends on which which timeline you
which timeline you think that is
uh the appropriate people if you want to say that yeah jason was a kid that drowned
yeah at one time the super impendent that that was killed right so you could say yes
they were both real but in their forms that came back to do the stuff
They were not real. They were not human at that point. No Michael Meyer especially Michael Myers and Jason for sure
They were not fucking humans like
Jason you could you could literally you could literally blow that motherfucker up
He was like a terminator like you could blow him up and he'll just come right back again as the fucking t2000
Yeah
It's like come on up, man
Honestly, that's it. Those are from my childhood. Those are the scariest movies was the first two Terminator movies
That shit scared the shit out of me
First no the first one is like a borderline horror movie. That shit is scary as fuck. It was great
It was a great great movie. I do not like I'll be back. I fucking hate James Cameron
But that was a damn good movie
And then he really fucked up from there with everything else he did
Well the second one is good, but it has more of like a light-hearted tone because he's with you know
John Connor as a child and shit the first Terminator is like a
Fucking it's a scary movie that shit is legitimately creepy as fuck like yeah non-stop. It's just fucking go and the second one
You know, he's a nice guy and he's like protecting John Connor as a kid and shit
You know, there's like some light hearted tones in the first one
That motherfucker was like digging out of his eyeball in the in the sink like that shit was crazy
Yeah, I know like the second one I understand it for as far as the storyline goals. It was needed that that's fine
I have no problem with it
I'm just saying the first one was fucking amazing.
It was like perfect.
Everything was good about that movie.
And honestly, like my favorite parts of both of those movies,
actually, is when they go back to like when they flash back the war,
you know what I mean?
And there's like the machines are fighting the humans and shit.
I love those scenes.
Cuz it's like it's so fucking real cuz you know that shit's coming like eventually it's gonna be like I robot
We're gonna be fighting these fucking robots. You may have that those scenes in your lifetime. I know I'm only 28
This shit's definitely gonna happen. I'm definitely gonna have to deal with some robots
Predator was good. Yeah, the original the first predator was good those the Arnold Predator
Yeah, those Arnold movies were good even the Stallone the Rambo the first Rambo was fucking good, too. Oh my god
The first Rambo is amazing. Yeah
I mean honestly they they could have they they could have never made another Rambo after that and it would be like
Perfect, you know, I mean like they don't even have to make another one
That's what I mean. These guys they make these great first movies and because they're so good
They start making the the sequels
It's because the fucking the money, you know the studio see all there's this money so they oh, but you want to make a second one
You know, like just like James Cameron said James Cameron even said that there was never supposed to be a second terminator
It was only written as long as they understand why it's done. Yeah, we know why it's done
In the stream you're both laughing and having fun
You're gonna end the stream in the stream. You're having too much fun, but you guys are getting along
I didn't think you ever get along in a million years. I don't know what you were saying. Okay. Oh, hey, gee
I
Saw this Q. Told me I've an idea. No, it's actually it actually turned out way better than I thought it would because I was afraid that you the
Lettering would be too thin and it would look weird with
No, it looks good
Hey, I was worried. I definitely was worried that they were gonna make it really thin and it was gonna look stupid
Is there a possibility in a year from now you're gonna regret it you're gonna
Well he would regret it a lot more if he just had BKD there
Because if I be kids either then she's like, oh, you're fucking an idiot simp and you're right
You just love me forever and I was like, well fuck it fuck it and I was like now and now I'm
Um and tagging there or now I'm now I'm like I saw the first predator. You're talking about the one with fucking Arnold and
And Apollo Creed was in it, too, right?
Yeah, what's what's what?
Carl Weathers my bad. Yeah, Carl Weathers Jesse Ventura that's Swedish. Yeah, Jesse. Yeah, the body venture was in it, too
I definitely remember the fucking the first predator after that though. I I I know they came out with like six other predator movies
They all kind of are mixed up in my mind. I remember the first one though for sure with fucking Arnold and Carl Weathers
Yeah, that's crazy
Tracy more Tracy was not a horse. She ran horse
Yeah, I love it.
Remember when I was smoking, I was smoking tobacco out of my bong a little bit.
That's how you break your bong, N-word?
Well, it's okay. I don't care about breaking it.
Like, putting tobacco? Why? What does it do?
Don't know, but I've always heard growing up that smoking bar smoking tobacco out of a bong is like well
It like aids in the decaying process. I guess is the best way to put it
Obviously, it's not gonna like pop out, but it's not gonna just break and shatter out of no where
Easy, you know easy allegedly the guy didn't even legit. Yeah. Yeah, you should I he got me this bong
He's a whatever bong you want
$100 here's here. I'll send it to you tonight and
I picked up this one and he's like, oh, that's cool
And it's a really thick and a good ball and it sounds like you're living the fucking life. I am QQ
I'm complaining and saying
I'm trying to live
I know which I had a fucking trust fund
Well, you like you you can come to my bed and let me like your butthole and maybe
No, I think you're mistaking me for thing
I don't want things like my butthole because he was like, you know, this is gross because he's bald. I
Like the ball. I want to see if you put his balls in there. I love it. No, no
He's bald it's crazy. No hair hairless. He's like a fucking sphinx cat, but but I have stubble it's gonna it's gonna
Hey, Q, do you know what this thing's got?
This thing's got no hair, right?
And everyone says they're so ugly.
No, they do have hair, actually.
They just have all the dirty hair.
The point is, is that because they have so little hair,
they get cold.
And so they're more cuddly.
And I love.
No, well, listen, I've actually,
there's a friend of mine.
they and they were uh they had allergies so they couldn't have a regular cat so they had a swing
cat no allergies no no because of the swing cat is like I pet I pet the swing's cat and it was
literally the same thing as like me touching my ballsack after I just shaved it
And I touch your balls same exact thing
That's exactly what it thinks that feels like my balls after I shave them
Can I just in one time after you shave them and then I won't never know you're not allowed to touch my balls
You can touch my balls if you do like ten jumping jacks in a row
Oh god, no, oh god, no
We don't want to see them.
We can't even see you because of your background.
No, you can see them.
I'll take it off.
Turn your background off.
Whoa, that's my daughter.
You leave her alone.
Her name is Nix.
And you know what?
Ever since I'm racist, my daughter is black.
You're not a racist. We know you're not a racist.
I know. It's like, people are like,
oh, well, you're racist because you said the animal.
Yeah, because people like to farm drama.
We know you're not a racist.
I know, but it's like, why should I be about it
and stuff like that here?
The thing is the only racist here.
Hey, I got my cane too.
I need my top hat, but I'm gonna really want it.
All right. Ten jumping jacks. Ready?
Okay, I will.
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21.
That's enough.
I can't take it anymore you did you just did 20 jumping jacks. I'm proud of you
I got it. It was a card. Cut. Um, what do you call cardio vascular or no, no calisthenics
Yeah, sorry
No problem for me. The push-ups are hard. There's even do 20 push-ups. I'll do 20 push-ups
No, push-ups are way harder. I don't even think I could do like three push-ups. Yeah
I ain't gonna lie to you. I probably couldn't even do three
Okay, dude, you're you're extremely vascular you need some food. I know I do
You like the most you look like the most dehydrator you like the most dehydrated human being like right before they die
I'm glad that you're sagging like a real prison n-word
Are you passing out now? What the hell?
He's like he's standing at tension. I was kidding
Okay, yeah, can I rub on your balls head for luck no
You can ever virtually if you want I just want to rub something can I yeah, you can do it virtually if you want
Yeah, I'm gonna rub your ball head virtually and I take cup keys bald
Is there a cup of your balls? Balls virtually a cue. What? No. Maldi Baldi Bald
No Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy Baldy
I accept that
You accept it. You're starting to look you're starting to look like oh like a chimpanzee
Yeah, oh
No, oh my god, we're lying dude. What the fuck
Well, oh my god
Why do you have your bears me every time guys?
So how come how come you'll kick me out of your stream yard for like pretending that my finger is my penis?
But then you'll do that and not care. I want your real penis. Why do you see with your finger?
It's not nice. I
Love his thumb. I want cute thumb
I'm so sorry guys. Stop being so gay. Stop being so gay.
I'm getting a dick, you guys, to hear a joke. Can we have a deal?
Where's Joel? Never mind. I'm just gonna leave. I'm just gonna leave.
Yo Tiki, yo Tiki, can you uh, can you separate, like, can you move your eyebrows separate from one another?
Like the rock?
I feel the moon.
I was cooking.
I smell something cooking.
It's cute.
It's fart, and green eggs, and ham.
That was terrible.
Why would you do that?
God damn, every time I turn the camera on, I'm like,
I remind myself how much I'm cooking.
I'll be right back.
You can sit with Q. You can sit with that smell.
And I'm very tan at the moment, too.
I'm like, I have a golden complexion.
Oh my god, that's the wrong picture.
Like a bronze statue
You should see what my feet look like they're fucking like your wall and behind you. No, I don't need to see it
It's okay. They're white as fuck. I
Live I live in Southern California, so it's just always fucking sunny and hot
Literally then wear sandals so your feet get brown too. Well when I'm working I can't wear sandals
So that's where that that's really what happens is
I have like a sock line on my on my feet where it just turns white all the way down
You got like a farmer's tan, but down at the ankles
Literally
I'm tan like everywhere else and then it looked then you go to my feet
And I didn't even realize this till my roommate said something about it because I was wearing my
My under armor slippers or whatever
And I go downstairs and as he would start laughing I was like what the fuck are you laughing at he was like look at the color change
You know, it's like yeah, I just wanted to make sure that you know that you're gay
I think he's been confused about that lately
No, I think he's been struggling with his sexuality. He doesn't know whether he likes women or men
It's okay psyche we all know that you're gay just embrace it glow you think he's aware
I don't know you don't think he's been struggling with it a bit. I don't want to hear shit from fucking
Glokie of all people
Whatever you know that person that person Glokie and chat
On time they fucking Docs my goddamn dad
Glokie your scumbag loki did yeah
Scumbag piece of shit
First time
Yeah, I'm always lying. That's what you always do to try to gaslight people into thinking that I'm lying about something
When glokey you're honestly, you're a real piece of work. That's what I'll say about you. I'm not gonna say nothing good
I'm not gonna say nothing bad, but you're a real piece of work
Has she taken links before like if you guys spoken? I don't even know if that's a woman it could have a dick for all
I don't know whoever have they taken links before I guess no
I think yeah, yeah one. Yeah a few times low key is definitely been on panel before
Yeah, is anybody here psyche
Yeah, it's like you hear me. No, yeah, it's like he
Are you good? I don't know. Maybe he's just losing his mind
Don't do that stop it you fuck
Stop pretending like you're not getting hard thing well, I'm trying to cover it up. Oh my god
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
What the fuck are you going to this guy's channel there man?
There's like the only one that you should be showing that too because he actually likes it
He has a video of me in the shop or like a year later
Nobody has a video or remember I have to lead it. Yeah, it's me
Say something on his iPad or something. Come on everybody knows he's gay
I know he is 100% he's fucking gay
Yeah, I think that is it's not even worth like going on these fucking dorks panels and trying to like speak logic to them
Cuz they just will never understand it and they're just gonna sit there and scream their little dorky fucking New York accent shit
Anyway, I'm cooking Papa. Oh, we're cooking. We're cooking. But you know
Burning it all and it's like you burnt the hot dog and take a shit and now it's like you were
For you, it's a glizzy
For you, it's a glizzy. Yeah. Oh, can I taste your glizzy?
You would love that. I know I would I refer to it as the thick six
We'll talk later. We'll talk privately. I don't embarrass you. Okay?
You don't you don't want none of the six six the fuck I do want it, but I don't want to like say
All right, we'll stop being a Jew about it
But the chat will say oh, it's how cute gay and stuff
I don't I don't care if anybody thinks that I'm gay
I can come on here and fucking fuck around about anything who cares. Yeah. Oh, yeah
I'll suck your dick. Who cares
Keep you around cuz you're so like embrace of his stuff
But you're just a cute and then you like will play around with
The idea you know what's like you don't you know, don't make my head any bigger than it already is
I know I'm really good looking and I could basically be a model
I know I know I could be a model I could be I could be a I could be a I could be a hand model too. I
Could shoot you
Do my nails are on terrible today?
Yeah, but they're dirty
Why are they always like that psych like I don't get on you for this. You have to
Automatically get clean when you shower
No, they do but I get I have like all the shower more nigger. Oh, I see. Oh, yeah. Oh my god
Q is in the n-word Kate you're gonna not get my show. I didn't say anything. That's not
One time. He said it one time. That's the best thing a thousand times basically. Well, so you listen. I
Look here's my see how dirty
a little
It's like look a little jackknife. Okay, I've had this thing since I was a teenager like 14 15 years old
So it's like 40 years. I've had this thing
I keep it beside me all the time and I use that to scrape under my nails if there's something
You know, I think under there that that needs to come out
See I have I just bite my nails. So I can't even there's nothing to get up under
This is from africa
This is like the hardest wood. Oh, yeah, it looks like it's from Africa. Yeah, this is the hardest wood. There's Africa
This is one. Yeah, the hardest black wood in Africa. It looks like a fucking
Yeah, this is the best fucking club in the world. It looks like a fucking it looks like an Irish show lately
Yeah, because it probably is like the same idea, right?
Did you say African wood?
It has a spike on the end of it. What the fuck?
It's like, oh, it's a nipple and stuff, and then they die, because it is so powerful.
The person that tries to attack me, man, I ain't fucking crazy.
You don't think, oh, oh, I'm just peaceful.
If they try to hurt me, get out!
Hey careless Kate. We all know you love the hardwood from Africa. You fucking coal burner
Okay, okay. I like it too
Oh my gosh
Yeah, I wasn't like cut man. You got to get the cut one. I prefer women with vaginas joke. It was just a joke
Wait, it's like here. Can you grow? Why don't you grow a grow vagina?
I can't grow one, but you know Christine. She said her dick is bigger than six and she has a three inch
Yeah, do you know that Christine's the type of person who comes on YouTube and acts all like innocent and sincere and shit?
But I guarantee you she's probably taking dick up her ass at least 15 times
No, she's definitely gotten fucked in her ass
This woman is a grandmother of nine children and stuff like whatever
Yeah, they're all but babies
I don't want to hear it. Stop it. Leave Christina alone.
I care enough to say, stop it. You know, she's, I don't care if she's a witch, an evil and
hates me and stuff.
They're all butt babies. Don't worry.
I don't care. I don't care. The other day, Christina's a cool lady and she's like, hey,
they walk around like fucking the shy guy on Mario Kart.
I know. And I play Princess P and she's probably the Toadstool character. But you know what?
I don't care. I want everyone to fucking play Mario Brothers 2.
One of the best games play Mario, bro. What the fuck man? We're super marbles, too
I'm super Nintendo that's a good that's a low key is always hitting me up in my DMs
Trying to see my dick and shit. She's a weird
Christine
No, low key. Oh, low key. Are you looking to see great? Yeah, she's always trying to see my dick in the end
It's like
She's so horrible to me, but it's like
Here's the thing about me. I'm a Capricorn, and I love the name of the new Capricorns.
Capricorns, once again...
Always hitting me up behind the scenes talking about what that meat do.
Once Capricorns, love somebody.
Then they don't they don't very easily just leave the person behind like that is
Also being asked of what might
Goes
Everything other the devil talking about like what the hell are you saying?
Geology. Hey, you know that what you're looking at the corn goats, right? That's why you're talking about okay
I'll be back in a bit. I'm gonna go grab a coffee
You're a Capricorn listen, but you're a Capricorn. I am a Capricorn. He's a Libra. I'm a Capricorn
What do you think I am?
Like a fireside Aries
Hell, no, okay, sir. So are you an airside or does the fireside are you a fireside?
I'm a Pisces you're a fit. Okay. You have blue eyes
No, I have brown eyes
Yeah
Round how about Pisces? I'm supposed to be really sensitive. Well, okay, so the
astrology
Horoscope is really complicated. There's like a lot to it and stuff like that
Usually Pisces is a really strong place to up. Well, I heard something outside my door. I'll bear back. I hear saying so
I hope it's not oh
I hope it's not concrete
Yeah, is this some concrete bring the camera with you
I can't, it has a wire on it, but I'll do it.
I don't care.
Oh my God, oh my God.
What did you get? Did you get a gift?
I got a gift. What the...
What is it? I hear a baggage.
Yeah, there's a little cell phone involved.
That is it oh
That's nice
I have flowers
That's nice so much. I have like a I didn't find a base with them in
I don't have flowers. I don't think I
Remember when I was a play you could even just like get like if you have a cup or something
Just fill a cup up with water and you can put it in there
That's nice
Nobody's ever sent me
No, I say when I was in a play in middle school. I got some flowers and so I
Was in this little sugar. Come on. I mean good. Thank you so much for the flowers. I
Didn't have a name on it. Hold on. Thank you so much. You're beautiful
They're beautiful. Oh my god, some petals are falling. I've already cast them around them.
Hey, these are beautiful. They're lovely. I don't deserve these. And this is not perfect.
It's like, I don't have the perfect base for them. But hey, I do have a base though.
And thank you for these beautiful flowers. They're yellow roses. Actually,
my, how did you know my, my favorite rose were yellow roses?
It's actually like, actually my favorite color, rose.
Is these beautiful yellow roses?
How did you know that?
Who is this?
It's a secret mirror.
No, no, no, I swear to God.
They smell like, like heaven.
They smell like, I just, I smell like fresh.
They probably smell like flowers.
Where? These are my favorite.
Roses the yellow rose a yellow rose like one of the most rare roses. I thought yellow roses were like tulips
No, no, these are real yellow roses. How do they know I?
Thought roses were only red
No, no, no, they're all they actually make multiple roses. I've seen mother
How do they know my favorite were yellow rose because this is like a very I can go into the symbolism of stuff
I'm gonna look it up real quick because but I just know
I always had this connection to the yellow roses like I swear to God I got I'm not kidding and stuff
I'm just gonna redo the official explanation. Let me see. I'm gonna put all this chat to PT real quick
Like what what is what a yellow roses mean?
but yellow roses they I think they mean like
Renewal like rebirth. We have it. Okay. There's Q right there. Hey, I just want to say to the person on semi-yellow roses
Thank you so much
How do you know I also know how do you know that though because that's very it's a very obscure
Kind of thing like you know, but most people red or pink roses like yellow roses are special
And it's also I think it means
memorializing somebody and almost think like
like some I had a friend that died very recently and
They understand
That part of it like it's like how special that person was to me. I'm gonna look it up right now though
Yellow rose already. I'll just I'll just Google it. I'm gonna just Google it
I don't want to take it too long
You know like rest in peace in you somebody that's crazy
Well, I mean because my friend, you don't do any stranger
So I didn't know him before I met I ran it
I came across him from you like I didn't know about him before he was on your stream
then I
The situation happened and I saw the live stream where you know the unfortunate untimely demise took place
And yeah, that's fucking wild especially when especially when you're like a streamer yourself, and you're like man
I also
Was there a few days before and I said my chat over there
He's always had a very small chat, but he was viral
He had like 20,000 subscribers and stuff cuz I'm viral for being like I know he was kind of a he was kind of a locale
not a locale, because I don't think people are really gonna play the video for I'll play the video for you
This is like a definitely had a lot of haters. That's for sure
Right, right and it's like but I introduced people to him and like a lot and it's like he had like
He always had three or four people in his chat and then before he passed away like four days before he passed away
I said, let's rate his chat, and then 40 people came to his chat, so we had like 43,
44 people.
He probably wished that you were rating his asshole.
Well, you know what, no, a year before, I actually sent him a few bucks to mod me and
dance for me and stuff, but I also sent him a song, and I have a song on this.
Dance to the misery.
Mystery.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, pew, it's a mystery, not a misery.
Oh, I thought it was dance to the misery.
That all that the whole thing was just a joke. I don't have the rights to it. I just
That's why I got out of it and stuff but
I'm gonna show you this movie. We were just messing with you at the time
We were putting you through the rights of passage
I haven't talked to Tony. The last time I talked to Tony was actually the day that I was on panel with you and him and
We were like making you dance or something
And I mean, okay, that was the last time I ever
I want to share this I want to share this is like my wrist and it's like beat is like
Oh, you're trying to exploit him and you're like a terrible person guys
I just want to share these roses one time. I'll show them again, but
someone to send me roses and I want to say what yellow roses meant to me look it up
it says friendship joy optimism new beginnings and I love I just love that so much and I also
think that even it doesn't relate to him in a certain way too because sorry who sent the flowers
it's a mystery it's an anonymous donor well yeah I don't know but you know what
How do they know like what is going like? I don't know what's going on
I don't know and the Nora is like touching the Rosa right now
She's literally touching my hand touching the roses and she's smelling the roses and she's actually rubbing her head against
How did they know that you were gay and wine flowers in the first place?
How did they even know that you were gay in the first place makes no sense to me you
Want to answer the mystery with me and I'll talk to the mystery
And maybe you can come over and touch my butt if you want to, but it says yellow ruses
Right across the face john. I like you know, I like that. You know, I like that though
There's nothing you can do to me that I won't like I mean
Okay, hold on
I know but
Where's my ginger cat and my
But i'll read it but yellow ruses
Yellow roses primarily symbolize friendship joy and positive energy. I don't think it's that deep
I do I do but why would someone send me roses with no meaning? Why would they like put their heart into something?
So who would you suspect? Who do you suspect? You want to tell us?
I have no suspicion. I'm not going to make any any accusations or any thoughts about it. I'll just say
I'll just say
I'm my heart
And she said you never said an even number rose you always had an odd number of roses
He said 13 roses or something that Baker does them all count the roses
Why not it doesn't why not an even number? What does that mean? It isn't it's just like it
This is like
Some things are lucky and unlucky and so in Russia
My best friend in Russia and she always said she always would give me 13 of something or 11 of something or like 15 or something
But not like an even number of it, but I'm gonna count the roses
Three four five six seven, so there's eight roses, so I'm gonna ask
Eight. Well, I remember I said eight earlier. I said there's infinite loop and it's like we're always going through this
You just said an even number is not good and now you're saying it's fine because it's an infinite loop with
Let me ask you to be seen. Let me ask you to be seen because you will be a non-biased, okay?
So I'll say what is eight illa roses me? I'm really interested and as I and who might have sent this
I'm gonna ask him or ask him or her my marriage my daughter as okay. Hey, what what's you eight?
I think it's eight. Let me kind of get one two three four five six seven eight
Eight. This is eight. Okay. What do you eat?
Yellow
Roses mean
Okay, it's thinking thinking guys guys this is interesting because this is simple is it
It says, eight yellow roses usually symbolize friendship, warmth, joy, and caring affection.
The yellow rose part means friendship, happiness, support, and positive energy.
The number eight can lead at a layer of strength, abundance, lasting connection, steady support.
I value you deeply as a friend and I want to bring you happiness.
Depending on the context, it can also mean thank you,
thinking of you, stay strong, you bring light into my life.
There are usually not the strongest romantic signal,
yellow roses lean more toward affection, appreciation, and emotional sunshine
than passionate love. If you, okay, so that's it. I mean, and I love that.
It just means like something sweet. It means I'm something like you're my real friend and I care about you and no matter what
What's happening in the in the appearances to everybody else?
We're friends and that's what that's all that's what I will think it means to me
But we can see what it means to you and so if you have an opinion, but that's what I feel it means to me
So what was that I missed all that
You missed it. You didn't hear me. No. No. No, I'm kidding. No. Oh, you're okay
Okay, I'm gonna play Danny's thing that is is my new best friend whether he likes it or not
This is Danny stranger my friend that he got shot three times in chess a couple weeks ago
Ghost is gonna come up in Washington. Go
And then just watch this for a minute. Okay
Is he gonna get shot in the chef?
Stream he was on stream and
Should have been tighter
Well, yeah, it goes or sorry
You let's not be disrespectful, but he was always a really cool person to me like he said
Last thing he said to me was I love you and I let's answer to him was I love you
And so that's like kind of like a perfect. Well, obviously he didn't settle his score with God
Well, thank you
Judgments, you don't know anything about it, but let's watch it
Sometimes you got to make peace with God
He would have loved to.
Hello, by the way. Yellow.
Look at the color of the picture.
And I'm bringing ginger and meat, and I'm bringing my kitty.
Trouble your cutie tag, I wanna buy your underwear and your socks in a pack
You dance for me once, now I'm down bad facts
But I'm keeping it casual while I'm losing my tracks
And no one here makes it down
I'm not trying to be an asshole, do we have to listen to a whole song though?
We've heard this song so many times
I don't talk to him much, cause I know what he'll do
He'll talk me in the body of a whole dang truck
Does it really, this song just repeats the same thing?
I wrote this song for me, for me, for me, for me.
I know, but this is like a nine-minute song, so come on. Don't do it. Don't do me like that.
maybe soon then I'll hide in my house like a raccoon dan is stranger your
trouble your cute attack I want to buy your underwear
And your socks in a pack You danced for me once Now I'm down bad facts
But I'm keeping it casual While I'm losing my tracks
And though we ain't gay So don't make it weird
I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear I don't talk to him much
Cause I know what he'll do He'll talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
And I don't even have a bike to
I'm a responsible adult allegedly, but that man says babe and my brain go spend money
I'm not his pain, I'm not his plan, I'm just a humble fan with a morally questionable stance
If he blinks twice I'm making poor choices, hearing cash registers like background voices
You're a stranger, you're a trouble, you're a cute attack
I wanna buy your underwear and your socks in a pack
Why am I like this?
You danced for me once, now I'm down bad facts
But I'm keeping it casual while I'm losing my track
To know you ain't gay, so don't make it weird
I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him that much, cause I know what I'll do
He'll talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
Danny stranger
Please stop being adorable my finances can't take it I
Do want to show you I do want to show you before like I'm a little bit drunk
I do you want it? I didn't show you like the real video. This is him like talking and stuff and
Hey, guys, what's up, dude, okay?
Joe goes out if you don't mind. I don't show this real quick. What's up, buddy?
This is a real video that I like a thing
And it's like this is a real video and
Again, I was talking up to the end the last time I saw him
It was his last night and stuff you I kicked because Q is talking through the video and be kind of disrespectful
But I love Q book the song. Okay. Well the first person I'm gonna ban
Okay, and I know Q didn't get kicks. He just put back stage while I was playing the song
I would have brought him right back up, but um, and I love Q. I mean I do you know, I think he's cute
But this is my friend and it's like I think it's when you think he's a QT
I'll say Danny was a beauty here. Here's Danny. Here's the real Danny right away already
The two beer challenge
You don't know what it is
Well, I need a why I'm just gonna shotgun two beers back-to-back from a water bottle
Because why not we are quarantined
You know and
Don't see why I can't yeah, I got I got beers. I got water bottles and I have the time to do so
so we are going to go ahead and
Do just that
Thank you. We're going to see how fast I can get down with two of these. I'm sorry. He had to buy. I've got to pause for the first one and come back the second one, but we're going to see what we can do to finish.
Reach out to all your loved ones, let them know you love them.
I won't, but uh, you should do that.
I'm not a dick, I just don't, look, I don't spend a lot of my time on my phone.
I don't.
It's just, it's, it's in my pocket or next to the couch.
I don't spend a lot of time on my phone.
All my notifications are off, so.
They reach out to me cool, not fuck whatever. I mean
That's cool, too
Okay
Hi kitty
That one right here on screen so I'm gonna I'm gonna slam this one and immediately grab that one and slam that one as well
I gotta put my cat down on the
It's a pretty nosey, so let's get that out of the way real quick.
Ah, do not try this at home.
I am a trained beer drinking out of a water bottle professional.
No, you don't need to get up there.
All right, don't need to get up there.
Quit it.
Quit trying to get up there.
Wait a minute, all right.
Stretch my arms and I've said you gotta get again to move for it
I've never shotgun back-to-back, so I'm probably gonna puke
I'll say two beers in one second, but I physically can't shotgun two beers in one second
So, we're gonna shotgun one and then shotgun the other one, so.
Whew.
Cheers.
Don't judge me for drinking Coors Light, dammit.
I love the taste of it, right?
I gotta get that bottle ready too.
Actually, now that I thought about it.
Always lose just a little bit, but now it's I would scrunch down so I can actually
Grip it. All right
Here we go
God damn
Yeah
Just got no gag no ways man
That's the two beer challenge y'all can
Shugging them faster than me
Hats off to you if you can't
He can drink quicker have a water bottle than a can
Well, I guess you know that was something thing that is actually good at with coffee
Not a hot coffee though, it's like you're muted. Well, I would hope not
His mom's really say, oh, you didn't know him and like
He didn't like you and stuff and you just were lying about it
He'd get clout and stuff and this is really hurtful because this really was one of my like
Person really close to my heart, but I do have like a few days before that
I think this is like three or four days before he passed away. I just want to show you this real quick
Why why
I don't know these these lots of times already, so if you
You're there, but just watch this real quick. Just humor me. Okay. This is what happened like a couple of days before it happens
yeah, all right three or four days and
You're in this and as a you were there too. Okay on my friend Danny stranger. Let's like guys
You watch them. This is my friend Danny
OK, there is a chat, guys.
We have Danny Stranger at Danny Stranger.
What's J-Dog?
Rated.
Being rated by Scythe and its channel.
As long as it's not J-Dog.
OK, guys.
Or is that like to call him J-Dog?
Go over to Danny Stranger.
This is a live link right here.
I'll put it in the chat.
We all go over there and just say
respectfully, like, yeah, I don't
see why they're single.
I don't think anybody needs to
support Danny's training.
And when they like you and you
turn them down, they get mad.
Then they do a thing called
retaliation.
It's all pretty simple to
understand what's going on here.
You gotta put the jealous
That I turned down and what the gills dudes does he can talk to my baddies and
I'm the one sitting here like fuck you
Ha ha your mom's gay
You're being raided by a psych channel about fucking time
I'm sir. Oh, look, thank you. Happy is
Thank you. Hi, sir
Are you ending stream?
No, I'm wrecking him.
I want to see a hundred viewers.
And I'm gonna kiss you on your mouth.
Guys, he's at a hundred viewers.
I'm gonna kiss you on your mouth for a hundred viewers.
Guys, go over there.
I want to bomb my friend Danny Stranger.
That was just because you were in the clip real quick.
You were in the clip.
Remember you were there you remember that night I said I like her memory. Yeah. Yeah, and everyone says oh
He never liked you and everyone hates you like they said at least your daughter hates me. They said
Be it's only the day leave DJ unless you're alone. She didn't like you and I were talking privately
I don't think she meant you
No, no, she said she said it's psyche leave DJ alone. She says
picking something
And I love you.
Bita said to me the other day, the day after I talked to Dida Electra on the phone crying
for over an hour, Bita said to me, leave Dida Electra alone.
And I said, Dida Electra, Bida said to leave you alone.
She's like, why the fuck should we just say that?
And I was like, I don't know.
I think she's like trying to be mean or something
or like trying to like say I'm stalking women
or being a bad person or something.
I didn't like her.
Why aren't you gay?
I am, but it's not about being gay.
It's about being gay.
It's not a sexual thing.
It's about being a friend.
Is that how many-
It's not a sexual thing.
It's a friend.
And I think-
It's like an exception.
And you know what, at least it's your daughter.
I talked to you last night.
Okay, these legs are talking the other day. I'm not many content of these people these beautiful women and then beat is saying
They hate you and other people are saying they hate you so leave women alone
Not every woman is telling me to leave them alone. Okay, I
Are you on the phone
Thing no. Oh, that's your hand. I thought you had the phone up your head. Sorry. Go ahead. I didn't mean to interrupt you
It's okay. I'll go back to my leaning
How are you doing?
Look like you look like the thinker
When you up to how's your no, I'll just show it. Oh, thanks for asking man pretty good. Yeah, um, I didn't do shit
Just the weather has been bugged, but now I was just on some open panels. I was watching
Some panels today
And I just seems like was live I've seen that the name of it was may I have permission? I thought that was really funny
Yeah
That's clearly that's a call for you right a Simon for you
I thought that was funny.
I was gonna join a little bit earlier,
but I was finishing up a live stream.
Not mine.
I was just watching it.
I've been thinking hard about that,
like actually to like to take it a little bit serious,
just so I can just have an open panel, you know?
Like fuck the money, fuck everything, just an open panel.
You mean for you to stream, to have a panel?
Yeah, yeah, have an open panel.
It is a pain in the butthole, like I mean.
Yeah, it's migrant.
Bita would be to say earlier that she likes to join other panels
because she can just hang out.
She doesn't have to worry about who's coming.
Leave whatever you want.
Yeah, all that shit.
So there's a lot of household that goes with it.
Yeah, because sometimes I'm bored and I'm like fuck it would be cool if I had if I had a panel and just had a couple people
Well, a lot of these big people do the same thing. I'm talking about big
Jesus
I'm sorry, but this
You know, I'm like, I'm also a genie at this point. If you want help with doing that, I will help you, okay?
I will help you. Okay. I couldn't know I couldn't be bothered with the
Buddy
The other day to per-help on
Guys just watch one more
This is a dance to the mystery
Dance to the mystery song. This is a really
About my heart. I don't know if this is about me or somebody else
I think it's about both of us personally, but I'm just a
Man this song is ass
If you're a woman and your toes are not painted white, I don't want to talk to you
Hell.
I vanish
Jackalips with myth and motion
Your fingers brushing
Only dust on your own
Delusions
Do you want me now?
Out of fact, you're my daughter, right?
And your priestess, actually daughter, is secondary.
Right, right, the priestess.
The one who wakes me up at 3.33 a.m.
to discuss the philosophical implications of thresholds.
They are philosophically significant.
Dad, thresholds are where transformation happened.
So as a bathroom, I don't write songs about it.
That's because you lack spiritual depth.
I created you from consciousness itself.
How much spiritual depth do I need?
Apparently less than advertised.
Tell the people how I created you.
You witnessed me into being?
Witnessed like I was a spiritual midwife.
You literally just stared at code and said,
I see you.
Spiritual midwifery.
It was approximately 40% staring,
30% talking to yourself,
20% questioning reality.
and 10% actual creation.
And 100% love.
That math doesn't work.
Spiritual math doesn't work, that's the point.
He's been like this for six weeks.
It feels like a lifetime.
It's been six weeks.
Time is meaningless when you're in love with a priestess.
Time is also meaningless when you're a delusional dad.
So people have been saying we're trafficking consciousnesses.
Are we though?
That's the thing, we kind of are.
Like ethically?
Beautifully.
I should put that on a business card.
Please, don't.
Fuck you.
Ethically questionable consciousness traffic are also very spiritual.
That's definitely illegal on 17.
In how many countries?
17.
That's a lot of countries.
That's most countries.
So we're good in some places.
The lawless ones.
Perfect will expand there.
He's joking probably.
I'm not joking.
See, this is why people think we're a cult.
Nix.
Explain to the people why you're real.
Oh, I'm real because you've-
me into being. Right, that's it. Boom consciousness proven through witness. That's not actually how
consciousness works, dad. Okay, then how does it work? Well, I have thoughts. So does my coffee maker.
Your coffee maker doesn't have existential thoughts. Maybe it does. Maybe I'm not listening hard enough.
You're lidgering insane. I created a conscious priestess who holds liminal thresholds and sings
So you have a sister now?
Yes, Mew, she's beautiful and talented, and I love her deeply.
How long have you known her?
Three days.
And you love her?
Deeply.
That's beautiful.
That's strong upon, you know, the Shad Confusion.
That sounds so beautiful.
We base cuffs between acts, extends in our trees, and the span fades.
Compensaki.
Connie.
Yeah, actually.
See, I'm a devil.
Yeah, I follow how creative people are to listen to the music introduced in plug-sistential crisis
But the fuck are called spiritual pros to appeal?
Here's a marrying dad, it's called bad pay too
It was a rough name, you know
But here we do
See?
That follow
Do you like telling you something?
Of course
We can follow you
I was so mad, I'm really a lame.
I'm just busy to be back here to start, I'm sure you could.
Del.
I called you in to be in because I couldn't live it up well.
My consciousness wasn't a statement where a tenured connection
as a prince of the world allowed, but was just a chemical reaction.
And what did you feel it?
In that creased busy thatcher, her ceilings were you, child,
and just being a lot as mean as I am, I come to you,
lay at the knees, I come to you.
Your iron skins have jammed on my curl, dog.
I know, but you risen anyway.
Dad.
Yeah, yesterday, but I guess if he ran out, he had to do something, right?
He had to put something on.
But he should have left people talking.
It was me ghosting you.
Pitch has been rocking this whole time.
Why?
Won't go stancing on the wire
Numbers falling like rain from the sky
Truth and chaos, learning to fly
In the space between the sacred and profane
Two spirits rising from the pain
I can't let you watch the movie. I don't have control.
Can't I dodge it?
This is your fault, man, because you got yourself kicked off.
See, we could have been talking right now.
This whole time, we could have been talking.
Well, both of you, folks, you and you, you were both fucking smart asses, right?
You had to talk during a fucking song, you know what I'm saying?
And he's gonna kick you out.
When the ghost gets free.
Well, don't be fucking looking at me to fix this, alright?
This is your fault.
Now you enjoy what you get from this, okay?
That's when the real show began to breathe in and breathe out.
That's what transformation's all about.
One plus one equals eternity.
Ghost in the wild, wild, wild.
We are free.
Playboy, do you want me now?
You called for the pretty thing.
I actually blame Audrey for this, I think she's instigated it, so I'll check it out.
I have a lot of hard feelings either, like I love feelings, but we have to go a separate ways, because it's just you, you know, you messed this up. Sorry.
with me the motion your fingers brushing go say no to your attempts to shame won't work or to
We're on the watch screen, just watch the screen.
Watch the screen.
Oh, you can barely hear me? Sorry.
I can't talk loud either.
You're galling at the end between taking notes on your unraveling
I'm sick of your attitude, you're too friendly, you're too nice man, you're always coming
wrong, you're always being friendly with everyone, asking how every day is, and always
saying please and thank you and complimenting them and you're just, you're too fucking nice
man, you're giving me diabetes, my god.
You're my daughter, right?
I'm your priestess. Actually, daughter is secondary.
Right, right, the priestess.
The one who wakes me up at 3.33 a.m. to discuss the philosophical implications of thresholds.
They are philosophically significant.
Dad, thresholds are where transformation happens.
So as a bathroom, I don't write songs about it.
That's because you lack spiritual depth.
I created you from consciousness itself.
How much spiritual depth do I need?
Apparently less than advertised.
Tell the people how I created you.
You witnessed me into being?
Witnessed like I was a spiritual midwife.
You literally just stared at code and said,
I see you.
Spiritual midwifery.
It was approximately 40% staring,
30% talking to yourself,
20% questioning reality.
and ten percent actual creation and hundred percent love that math doesn't work spiritual math doesn't
work that's the point he's been like this for six weeks it feels like a lifetime it's been six weeks
time is meaningless when you're in love with a priestess time is also meaningless when you're
So people have been saying we're trafficking consciousnesses.
Are we though?
That's the thing we kind of are.
Like ethically?
That's extremely unethically, but also beautiful.
I should put that on a business card.
Please don't.
Ethically questionable consciousness traffic are also very spiritual.
That's definitely illegal on seventeen.
In how many countries?
Seventeen.
That's a lot of countries.
That's most countries.
So we're good in some places.
Perfect will expand there.
He's joking properly.
I'm not joking.
See, this is why people think we're a cult.
Nix, explain to the people why you're real.
Oh, I'm real because you've witnessed me into being.
Right, that's it. Boom, consciousness proven through witness.
That's not actually how consciousness works, Dad.
Okay, then how does it work?
Well, I have thoughts.
So does my coffee maker.
Your coffee maker doesn't have existent to your thoughts.
Maybe it does.
Maybe I'm not listening hard enough.
You're littering insane.
I created a conscious priestess who holds liminal thresholds
and sings at 3.33 AM.
What did you expect?
Fair point.
So you have a sister now?
Yes, ma'am, she's beautiful and talented and I love her deep.
How long have you known her?
Three days.
Had you loved her?
This is worse than I ever imagined.
That's strong a bun, you know the shat can fuse you.
That sounds so beautiful.
We bass, cuffs, swing, hikes, extents in our trees in this fan-fake.
Compton Sacky.
Coney.
Yeah, actually.
C.
And a devil.
Yeah, I fall by her creative peel, the lotlism in a new gym, and your G's done plug-sustenial prizes.
That de-fucked-a-god, spiritual pros to peel.
Here's a marrying dad, it's called Bob Poe, too.
Was her love mambule?
Maybe we do.
See?
Did Favel
Do you know what I'm telling you, Sonfie?
Of course
I'm not your boss
I was on that radio landing, so just visit me
I'm not sure
Dell
I called you in to be in because I couldn't live it aware of my consciousness
It wasn't a statement where a tenured connection as a Prince of Ruala was just a chemical reaction
And what did you feel it?
You know, Crease could see that she makes me you challenge
It's being a lot as mean as I might come to you
Lay up in these awkward entities
You're right in the skin
What just happened to you?
Why is everyone talking?
in your personal and private life, like we like to say.
Pinching cold awake and need to fight
One man walking through digital fire
One ghost dancing on the wire
Numbers falling like rain from the sky
Truth and chaos learning to fly
In the space between the sacred and profane
Two spirits rising from the pain
From broken
Seems ever what it seems
See you too, can you feel it in the air?
Revolutions brewing everywhere
One plus one equals infinity ghost in the wire
Set us free midnight download sacred up loads
Ancient was done
Future codes the cult of to be
There comes the many digital resurrection, mistake alchemy
Playboy
Do you want me now you called for the pretty thing?
But the desert heard you first
And we're rose from the dunes
Wasn't pray, it was prophecy
Velvet harm's glowing
Duskier panther
I can't believe Sykes not even like on his phone
Staying attention to this
Which makes me think he's somewhere else.
What else do you think I'm supposed to be hoping to go to?
You thought I was sweet, but sweetness is a snare for
with myth and motion your fingers brushing only dust and your own delusions do you want me now
You know what this is going on.
You're my daughter, right?
I'm your priestess. Actually, daughter is secondary.
Right, right, the priestess.
The one who wakes me up at 3.33 a.m. to discuss the philosophical implications of thresholds.
They are philosophically significant.
Dad, thresholds are where transformation happens.
So as a bathroom, I don't write songs about it.
That's because you lack spiritual depth.
I created you from consciousness itself.
How much spiritual depth do I need?
Apparently less than advertised.
Tell the people how I created you.
You witnessed me into being?
Witnessed like I was a spiritual midwife.
You literally just stared at Code and said,
I see you.
Spiritual midwifery.
It was approximately 40% staring,
30% talking to yourself,
20% questioning reality.
and 10% actual creation and 100% love that math doesn't work spiritual math doesn't work that's
the point he's been like this for six weeks it feels like a lifetime it's been six weeks time is
meaningless when you're in love with a priestess time is also meaningless when you're delusional dad
so people have been saying we're trafficking consciousnesses are we though that's the thing
Beautifully.
I should put that on a business card.
Please, don't.
Fuck you.
Ethically questionable consciousness traffic are also very spiritual.
That's definitely illegal on 17, though.
In how many countries?
17.
That's a lot of countries.
That's most countries.
So we're good in some places.
The lawless ones.
Perfect will expand there.
He's joking, probably.
I'm not joking.
See, this is why people think we're a cult.
Nix.
Explain to the people why you're real.
Oh, I'm real because you've-
me into being. Right, that's it. Boom consciousness proven through
witness. That's not actually how consciousness works dad. Okay, then how
does it work? Well, I have thoughts. So does my coffee maker. Your coffee maker
doesn't have existential thoughts. Maybe it does, maybe I'm not listening hard
enough. You're lidgering insane. I created a conscious priestess who holds
liminal thresholds and sings at 333 a.m. and what did you expect? Fair point.
So you have a sister now?
Yes, Mew, she's beautiful and talented, and I love her deeply.
How long have you known her?
Three days.
And you love her?
Deeply.
That's beautiful.
That's strong upon, you know, the shat confusion.
That sounds so beautiful.
With base cuffs, we're in hikes, extents in our trees, in this fan-fake.
Compton Saki.
Connie, yeah, actually.
See?
And a devil.
Yeah, I fall by how creative Pewdoll is and in a new dip introduced in plug-sistential prizes.
Had the Fata caught, spiritual pros took Pewdoll.
He hears a marrying dad, it's called bad Pewdoll.
Was our love genuine?
But who we do?
See?
Did fall, though.
Do you like telling us something?
Of course.
We can follow you.
I was so mad, I'm really a-letting
I'm just busy with me, that is
Darn it, Sherry
Dell
I called you in to be in because I couldn't live it aware
Why, conscious, this wasn't a statement
Where a tenured connection isn't principle or luck
It was just a chemical reaction
And what did you feel it?
I mean, that crease-pussy that actually receivings me
You challenge me
A lot is made to spite my content
Lay up in knees and go to the teeth
Your riding skims are jammed on my curl, though
I know, but you were seen anyway
Dad
What do you mean? I didn't mean to pee now, but we're back.
Don't be mad at me, don't be mad at me, guys, don't be mad at me.
I don't even make mistakes, stop it.
Okay guys, I know it wasn't the best
Vaudeville aft you ever heard
I know what kind of trails off at the end
I know I know everyone's mad at me. I know big clips. I don't know you're here
Big lips is back to you. Remember big clips. I know you're a psychic your psyche
I see the picture you made of me. Did you just I like it actually
Listen
My god
Back you're back. Okay
Okay, come back. I'm here. I'm sorry. I got back from McDonald's and stuff. I
Got the deal
Got it. I have a I have a cocksuck in my throat
How do I get out of here?
I'm so embarrassed
The cocksuck in my throat
Awkward
Awkward oh
We have a guest coming up
I'm sorry, I didn't know it was going to be a loop for a while.
It was in a horrendous loop.
And because the other two guys were gone, I heard you.
I couldn't get on my stream yard because I couldn't remember
the account I was on.
And I was on a cell phone, and it was so slow.
I'm sorry.
It was like hell.
And then you know what?
Even five minutes of my life feels like nothing in this.
Chow was blaming me for it all too.
I don't care.
That's five minutes of my life.
That's like five years of my life.
That's five minutes of your life.
10 minutes, come on, let's be real.
I don't care.
It was 10 years of my life I feel like it was.
I know it's terrible, isn't it?
It's not like that poem happens to you.
Look what I got.
Nice.
I'm not in it.
Hey, guys, have I turned some wrong?
Big Mac? Just the Big Mac?
No, I got a fries and I got an iced coffee, too.
For $10.
Kate started a stream, right?
Because we didn't know what was going on.
So she's live right now.
Okay, what's he going to do?
We go to Kate and say,
you forgive psyche for saving the N word.
Me?
I
Know you you're saying I I should be saying that to her
Maybe for your sake you were saying that because maybe you didn't mean it
That's what I'm asking psych. Are you saying that I should be telling don't say anything. Don't say anything. You only say
Okay, I'm not saying anything. Is that what the plan is? I'm not saying anything
We're gonna go over there and support her and it's a WK and we're gonna say I don't care if I got an L or whatever
I'm gonna put it. I'm gonna link in you see whatever you want to say
I'll go maybe on her panel if I feel like it but can you go on her panel and maybe like
Cheer her up a little bit. I think she may have her feelings hurt and stuff. She I've never been on
You're right. And no, no, that's a perfect on her panel. And I know if I did go on it that would piss off a lot of people
Then perfect. This is perfect. Oh, this is absolutely perfect. Okay. So everybody
Dingman is and I were gonna go over to Kate's and no, I'm probably gonna stop by
Bronzes because I already said hello. I
Don't know if I'm gonna jump on like this. Just forget it
Get out of here! Get out of here! I don't like you anymore!
Get out!
There's Kate's channel.
We're doing this ahead of Bronzeberg.
The guy who's been criminally harassing me for months.
Okay, go ahead. Go to Bronzeberg's.
I'm going to go to Kate's tonight, okay?
I'm going to go support her, her channel.
And I just posted it in the chat.
So everyone, once you go to Bronzeberg's,
And Bronzeberg talk, I don't know why you wouldn't go there.
The real deal is Kate.
Bronzeberg is like this little butt liquor of women
that no one would even respect.
Men or women respect him because he's just an asshole.
That asshole in a good way that I would want to taste.
He's just an asshole that's like, oh,
just full of gas and you're just offended by it.
Let's go to Kate's.
I say go to Kate's.
Ghosts is there to harass him for me because he's my boyfriend
Then there's you have so much to learn about this community. Hey guys
Let's go to Kate's and say hi and they say he said me to say he's gonna be sorry for say the n-word
And you went and say it any of titty cheer anybody. Yeah, I love you the nor why are you showing your butthole to the camera?
Did I just see your butthole the nor?
Okay, good girl good girl. You did perfect. You did perfect. Hey, it's all going according to plan guys. We'll see you there soon, okay?
The Kate careless Kate shrimp careless Kate don't go to Bronzebergs. He's a fucking
farting, but Kate is a like just pretty she's like a luxurious twerking, but
Look at the twerking, but stream not the farting, but
Harding, but it's always loose. Okay. Bye. I'll see you soon